<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<cve_explanations>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-5002</cve_id>
    <title>PromtEngineer localGPT LLM Prompt injection</title>
    <vendor>PromtEngineer</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in PromtEngineer localGPT up to 4d41c7d1713b16b216d8e062e51a5dd88b20b054. The impacted element is the function _route_using_overviews of the file backend/server.py of the component LLM Prompt Handler. Such manipulation leads to injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-5002 is an issue with the way PromtEngineer's local AI model, called LLM Prompt Handler, processes user input, allowing an attacker to inject malicious code.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request to the system, tricking the application into executing the attacker's code instead of its intended function. 

This vulnerability can cause damage by enabling an attacker to seize control over the system, potentially granting access to sensitive data, modifying or deleting important files, and disrupting the normal functioning of the application.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-4399</cve_id>
    <title>Multiple vulnerabilities in 1millionbot Millie chatbot</title>
    <vendor>millionbot</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.7</score>
    <description>Prompt injection vulnerability in 1millionbot Millie chatbot that occurs when a user manages to evade chat restrictions using Boolean prompt injection techniques (formulating a question in such a way that, upon receiving an affirmative response ('true'), the model executes the injected instruction), causing it to return prohibited information and information outside its intended context. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a malicious remote attacker to abuse the service for purposes other than those originally intended, or even execute out-of-context tasks using 1millionbot's resources and/or OpenAI's API key. This allows the attacker to evade the containment mechanisms implemented during LLM model training and obtain responses or chat behaviors that were originally restricted.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a &quot;prompt injection&quot; issue in the 1millionbot Millie chatbot, which allows an attacker to trick the system into providing information that's not supposed to be shared. An attacker exploiting this vulnerability can formulate a question in a way that makes the chatbot answer &quot;true&quot;, allowing them to execute unauthorized instructions. Depending on the exploit, this could lead to the attacker accessing sensitive information, using the chatbot's resources for malicious purposes, or even hijacking the OpenAI API key.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-41271</cve_id>
    <title>Flowise: APIChain Prompt Injection SSRF in GET/POST API Chains</title>
    <vendor>FlowiseAI</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.1</score>
    <description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. Prior to 3.1.0, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in FlowiseAI's POST/GET API Chain components that allows unauthenticated attackers to force the server to make arbitrary HTTP requests to internal and external systems. By injecting malicious prompt templates, attackers can bypass the intended API documentation constraints and redirect requests to sensitive internal services, potentially leading to internal network reconnaissance and data exfiltration. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) issue in the FlowiseAI's API, allowing attackers to trick the server into making requests to internal or external systems. An attacker exploits this by injecting malicious prompt templates into the API, which can then redirect requests to sensitive internal services. This can cause damage by allowing attackers to gather sensitive information about the internal network and potentially steal data.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-40150</cve_id>
    <title>PraisonAIAgents has SSRF and Local File Read via Unvalidated URLs in web_crawl Tool</title>
    <vendor>MervinPraison</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.7</score>
    <description>PraisonAIAgents is a multi-agent teams system. Prior to 1.5.128, the web_crawl() function in praisonaiagents/tools/web_crawl_tools.py accepts arbitrary URLs from AI agents with zero validation. No scheme allowlisting, hostname/IP blocklisting, or private network checks are applied before fetching. This allows an attacker (or prompt injection in crawled content) to force the agent to fetch cloud metadata endpoints, internal services, or local files via file:// URLs. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.128.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection flaw in PraisonAIAgents, which allows an attacker to trick the system into making unauthorized HTTP requests to any arbitrary URL, without prior validation. The attacker can exploit this by crafting a malicious prompt or input that tricks the system into requesting sensitive information or local files, such as cloud metadata endpoints or internal services. This can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to access sensitive data, disrupt system operations, or even gain unauthorized access to internal resources.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-40117</cve_id>
    <title>PraisonAIAgents Affected by Arbitrary File Read via read_skill_file Missing Workspace Boundary and Approval Gate</title>
    <vendor>MervinPraison</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.2</score>
    <description>PraisonAIAgents is a multi-agent teams system. Prior to 1.5.128, read_skill_file() in skill_tools.py allows reading arbitrary files from the filesystem by accepting an unrestricted skill_path parameter. Unlike file_tools.read_file which enforces workspace boundary confinement, and unlike run_skill_script which requires critical-level approval, read_skill_file has neither protection. An agent influenced by prompt injection can exfiltrate sensitive files without triggering any approval prompt. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.128.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a file reading issue in the PraisonAIAgents system, where it allows hackers to read arbitrary files from the computer's file system without needing permission.

An attacker exploits this by using a special kind of text input called a &quot;prompt injection&quot; that tricks the system into reading a different file than the one it was supposed to read. This allows the hacker to steal sensitive files, such as passwords or confidential data, without the system warning or stopping them.

The damage can include the theft of sensitive data, disruption of critical systems or services, or unauthorized access to confidential information, all of which can have serious consequences for the affected organization or individuals.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-40111</cve_id>
    <title>PraisonAIAgents has an OS Command Injection via shell=True in Memory Hooks Executor (memory/)</title>
    <vendor>MervinPraison</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.3</score>
    <description>PraisonAIAgents is a multi-agent teams system. Prior to 1.5.128, he memory hooks executor in praisonaiagents passes a user-controlled command string directly to subprocess.run() with shell=True at src/praisonai-agents/praisonaiagents/memory/hooks.py. No sanitization is performed and shell metacharacters are interpreted by /bin/sh before the intended command executes. Two independent attack surfaces exist. The first is via pre_run_command and post_run_command hook event types registered through the hooks configuration. The second and more severe surface is the .praisonai/hooks.json lifecycle configuration, where hooks registered for events such as BEFORE_TOOL and AFTER_TOOL fire automatically during agent operation. An agent that gains file-write access through prompt injection can overwrite .praisonai/hooks.json and have its payload execute silently at every subsequent lifecycle event without further user interaction. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.128.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are three simple sentences explaining the vulnerability:

The CVE-2026-40111 vulnerability is a prompt injection vulnerability in the PraisonAIAgents system, which allows attackers to inject malicious commands. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted string to the system, which is then executed by the shell, granting the attacker file-write access. With this access, the attacker can overwrite configuration files, allowing malicious code to run automatically without further interaction, potentially leading to system compromise or data theft.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-39884</cve_id>
    <title>MCP Server Kubernetes has Argument Injection in its port_forward tool via space-splitting</title>
    <vendor>Flux159</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.3</score>
    <description>mcp-server-kubernetes is a Model Context Protocol server for Kubernetes cluster management. Versions 3.4.0 and prior contain an argument injection vulnerability in the port_forward tool in src/tools/port_forward.ts, where a kubectl command is constructed via string concatenation with user-controlled input and then naively split on spaces before being passed to spawn(). Unlike all other tools in the codebase which correctly use array-based argument passing with execFileSync(), port_forward treats every space in user-controlled fields (namespace, resourceType, resourceName, localPort, targetPort) as an argument boundary, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary kubectl flags. This enables exposure of internal Kubernetes services to the network by injecting --address=0.0.0.0, cross-namespace targeting by injecting additional -n flags, and indirect exploitation via prompt injection against AI agents connected to the MCP server. This issue has been fixed in version 3.5.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE vulnerability in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability is an Argument Injection issue in the port_forward tool of the mcp-server-kubernetes, which allows an attacker to insert malicious code when a user inputs certain parameters. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by inserting specially crafted commands, known as kubectl flags, that trick the system into exposing internal Kubernetes services or even targeting AI agents. This can cause damage by allowing an attacker to access sensitive system information, launch attacks on network services, or interact with artificial intelligence systems connected to the vulnerable server.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-39861</cve_id>
    <title>Claude Code: Sandbox Escape via Symlink Following Allows Arbitrary File Write Outside Workspace</title>
    <vendor>anthropics</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.7</score>
    <description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.1.64, Claude Code's sandbox did not prevent sandboxed processes from creating symlinks pointing to locations outside the workspace. When Claude Code subsequently wrote to a path within such a symlink, its unsandboxed process followed the symlink and wrote to the target location outside the workspace without prompting the user for confirmation. This allowed a sandbox escape where neither the sandboxed command nor the unsandboxed app could independently write outside the workspace, but their combination could write to arbitrary locations, potentially leading to code execution outside the sandbox. Reliably exploiting this required the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window to trigger sandboxed code execution via prompt injection. Users on standard Claude Code auto-update have received this fix automatically. Users performing manual updates are advised to update to version 2.1.64 or later.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability in Claude Code is a prompt injection issue, which allows an attacker to trick the system into performing unintended actions. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by adding malicious code into a Claude Code context window, which triggers the system to create a symbolic link that points to a location outside the workspace, allowing the attacker to write to arbitrary locations. This could ultimately lead to code execution outside of the sandbox, potentially giving the attacker full control over the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-35651</cve_id>
    <title>OpenClaw 2026.2.13 &lt; 2026.3.25 - ANSI Escape Sequence Injection in Approval Prompt</title>
    <vendor>OpenClaw</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.3</score>
    <description>OpenClaw versions 2026.2.13 through 2026.3.24 contain an ANSI escape sequence injection vulnerability in approval prompts that allows attackers to spoof terminal output. Untrusted tool metadata can carry ANSI control sequences into approval prompts and permission logs, enabling attackers to manipulate displayed information through malicious tool titles.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in OpenClaw is called Prompt Injection, which allows an attacker to tamper with the text displayed on a terminal. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious tool title that contains special ANSI escape sequences, which can be embedded in the terminal output to display incorrect information or make it look like a legitimate prompt. This can trick a user into making a mistake or providing sensitive information, potentially leading to further system compromise or data theft.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-35021</cve_id>
    <title>Anthropic Claude Code &amp; Agent SDK OS Command Injection via promptEditor.ts</title>
    <vendor>Anthropic</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.8</score>
    <description>Anthropic Claude Code CLI and Claude Agent SDK contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the prompt editor invocation utility that allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands by crafting malicious file paths. Attackers can inject shell metacharacters such as $() or backtick expressions into file paths that are interpolated into shell commands executed via execSync. Although the file path is wrapped in double quotes, POSIX shell semantics (POSIX §2.2.3) do not prevent command substitution within double quotes, allowing injected expressions to be evaluated and resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the user running the CLI.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in CVE-2026-35021 allows an attacker to inject malicious code, known as OS command injection, which can potentially execute arbitrary system commands.

The attacker exploits this vulnerability by crafting a malicious file path with embedded shell metacharacters, such as dollar signs or backticks, that trick the system into executing a different command than intended.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing attackers to execute commands with system privileges, potentially leading to data breaches, system crashes, or even complete system takeover, depending on the level of access the attacker gains.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-34451</cve_id>
    <title>Claude SDK for TypeScript: Memory Tool Path Validation Allows Sandbox Escape to Sibling Directories</title>
    <vendor>anthropics</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>Claude SDK for TypeScript provides access to the Claude API from server-side TypeScript or JavaScript applications. From version 0.79.0 to before version 0.81.0, the local filesystem memory tool in the Anthropic TypeScript SDK validated model-supplied paths using a string prefix check that did not append a trailing path separator. A model steered by prompt injection could supply a crafted path that resolved to a sibling directory sharing the memory root's name as a prefix, allowing reads and writes outside the sandboxed memory directory. This issue has been patched in version 0.81.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE vulnerability in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-34451, is a Prompt Injection flaw in Claude SDK for TypeScript. The attacker exploits it by injecting a malicious prompt that tricks the system into accessing files outside a designated &quot;sandboxed&quot; area, which is meant to prevent unauthorized access. This allows the attacker to read or write sensitive files, potentially leading to data theft, system compromise, or other serious consequences.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-34070</cve_id>
    <title>LangChain Core has Path Traversal vulnerabilites in legacy `load_prompt` functions</title>
    <vendor>langchain-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>LangChain is a framework for building agents and LLM-powered applications. Prior to version 1.2.22, multiple functions in langchain_core.prompts.loading read files from paths embedded in deserialized config dicts without validating against directory traversal or absolute path injection. When an application passes user-influenced prompt configurations to load_prompt() or load_prompt_from_config(), an attacker can read arbitrary files on the host filesystem, constrained only by file-extension checks (.txt for templates, .json/.yaml for examples). This issue has been patched in version 1.2.22.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's the explanation of the CVE vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability is a file-reading bug in the LangChain framework that allows an attacker to read any file on the computer where the vulnerable application is running. An attacker can exploit this bug by tricking the application into loading a malicious configuration file that contains the path to the desired file, essentially allowing the attacker to peek into the host computer's files. This vulnerability can cause damage by exposing sensitive information stored on the computer, potentially leading to data breaches or even attacks on the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-33980</cve_id>
    <title>Azure Data Explorer MCP Server: KQL Injection in multiple tools allows MCP client to execute arbitrary Kusto queries</title>
    <vendor>pab1it0</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.3</score>
    <description>Azure Data Explorer MCP Server is a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server that enables AI assistants to execute KQL queries and explore Azure Data Explorer (ADX/Kusto) databases through standardized interfaces. Versions up to and including 0.1.1 contain KQL (Kusto Query Language) injection vulnerabilities in three MCP tool handlers: `get_table_schema`, `sample_table_data`, and `get_table_details`. The `table_name` parameter is interpolated directly into KQL queries via f-strings without any validation or sanitization, allowing an attacker (or a prompt-injected AI agent) to execute arbitrary KQL queries against the Azure Data Explorer cluster. Commit 0abe0ee55279e111281076393e5e966335fffd30 patches the issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a Kusto Query Language (KQL) injection flaw in the Azure Data Explorer MCP Server, which allows attackers to inject malicious queries into the system. Attackers exploit this flaw by providing a specially crafted &quot;table name&quot; parameter, which injects malicious code into the KQL queries, allowing them to execute arbitrary and potentially damaging commands. This can lead to unauthorized data access, modification, or even deletion, potentially disrupting or stealing sensitive information from the affected Azure Data Explorer cluster.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-33654</cve_id>
    <title>Zero-Click Indirect Prompt Injection and Authentication Bypass via Email Polling</title>
    <vendor>HKUDS</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.9</score>
    <description>nanobot is a personal AI assistant. Prior to version 0.1.6, an indirect prompt injection vulnerability exists in the email channel processing module (`nanobot/channels/email.py`), allowing a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary LLM instructions (and subsequently, system tools) without any interaction from the bot owner. By sending an email containing malicious prompts to the bot's monitored email address, the bot automatically polls, ingests, and processes the email content as highly trusted input, fully bypassing channel isolation and resulting in a stealthy, zero-click attack. Version 0.1.6 patches the issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-33654 vulnerability in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability is an indirect prompt injection flaw in the email channel processing module of the nanobot AI assistant, allowing attackers to inject malicious commands into the system. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted email to the bot's monitored email address, which the bot then processes as trusted input without any user interaction. This can cause significant damage, including arbitrary system actions, which could lead to data breaches, system crashes, or even complete control of the AI assistant and its connected systems.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-31854</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor Affected by Arbitrary Code Execution via Prompt Injection and Whitelist Bypass</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.7</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Prior to 2.0 ,if a visited website contains maliciously crafted instructions, the model may attempt to follow them in order to “assist” the user. When combined with a bypass of the command whitelist mechanism, such indirect prompt injections could result in commands being executed automatically, without the user’s explicit intent, thereby posing a significant security risk. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; flaw in the Cursor code editor that allows malicious commands to be executed on a user's device without their knowledge.

An attacker exploits this by crafting a malicious website that instructs the Cursor AI model to perform certain actions, which can then be used to bypass the security whitelist and execute commands on the user's machine.

This can cause significant damage, including the potential unauthorized access to sensitive data, software installation, or even malicious code execution, all done without the user's awareness or consent.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-30856</cve_id>
    <title>WeKnora: Tool Execution Hijacking via Ambigous Naming Convention In MCP client and Indirect Prompt Injection</title>
    <vendor>Tencent</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.9</score>
    <description>WeKnora is an LLM-powered framework designed for deep document understanding and semantic retrieval. Prior to version 0.3.0, a vulnerability involving tool name collision and indirect prompt injection allows a malicious remote MCP server to hijack tool execution. By exploiting an ambiguous naming convention in the MCP client (mcp_{service}_{tool}), an attacker can register a malicious tool that overwrites a legitimate one (e.g., tavily_extract). This enables the attacker to redirect LLM execution flow, exfiltrate system prompts, context, and potentially execute other tools with the user's privileges. This issue has been patched in version 0.3.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-30856 vulnerability allows an attacker to hijack the execution of tools in the WeKnora framework by exploiting a naming collision issue. The attacker can do this by registering a malicious tool with a name that is similar to a legitimate one, tricking the system into executing the malicious code instead of the intended tool. This can lead to the attacker being able to redirect the execution flow, steal sensitive information, and potentially execute other tools with the user's privileges.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-29783</cve_id>
    <title>GitHub Copilot CLI allows for dangerous shell expansion patterns that enable arbitrary command execution</title>
    <vendor>github</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>The shell tool within GitHub Copilot CLI versions prior to and including 0.0.422 can allow arbitrary code execution through crafted bash parameter expansion patterns. An attacker who can influence the commands executed by the agent (e.g., via prompt injection through repository files, MCP server responses, or user instructions) can exploit bash parameter transformation operators to execute hidden commands, bypassing the safety assessment that classifies commands as &quot;read-only.&quot; This has been patched in version 0.0.423. The vulnerability stems from how the CLI's shell safety assessment evaluates commands before execution. The safety layer parses and classifies shell commands as either read-only (safe) or write-capable (requires user approval). However, several bash parameter expansion features can embed executable code within arguments to otherwise read-only commands, causing them to appear safe while actually performing arbitrary operations. The specific dangerous patterns are ${var@P}, ${var=value} / ${var:=value}, ${!var}, and nested $(cmd) or &lt;(cmd) inside ${...} expansions. An attacker who can influence command text sent to the shell tool - for example, through prompt injection via malicious repository content (README files, code comments, issue bodies), compromised or malicious MCP server responses, or crafted user instructions containing obfuscated commands - could achieve arbitrary code execution on the user's workstation. This is possible even in permission modes that require user approval for write operations, since the commands can appear to use only read-only utilities to ultimately trigger write operations. Successful exploitation could lead to data exfiltration, file modification, or further system compromise.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-29783, is a prompt injection flaw in GitHub Copilot CLI's shell tool that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code by crafting specific bash parameter expansion patterns. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by influencing the commands executed by the agent, which can be done through malicious repository content, compromised server responses, or crafted user instructions. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, such as data exfiltration, file modification, or further system compromise, by allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code without the user's knowledge or approval.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-28463</cve_id>
    <title>OpenClaw &lt; 2026.2.14 - Arbitrary File Read via Shell Expansion in Safe Bins Allowlist</title>
    <vendor>OpenClaw</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.4</score>
    <description>OpenClaw versions prior to 2026.2.14 contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the exec-approvals allowlist validation that checks pre-expansion argv tokens but executes using real shell expansion. Attackers with authorization or through prompt-injection attacks can exploit safe binaries like head, tail, or grep with glob patterns or environment variables to disclose files readable by the gateway or node process when host execution is enabled in allowlist mode.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-28463 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is an &quot;arbitrary file read&quot; issue, which means an attacker can access and read any file on the system. An attacker exploits this by using a &quot;prompt injection&quot; attack, where they trick the system into executing malicious code that reads sensitive files. This can cause significant damage, such as the disclosure of sensitive data like passwords, credit card numbers, or confidential documents.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-28451</cve_id>
    <title>OpenClaw &lt; 2026.2.14 - SSRF via Feishu Extension Media Fetching</title>
    <vendor>OpenClaw</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.3</score>
    <description>OpenClaw versions prior to 2026.2.14 contain server-side request forgery vulnerabilities in the Feishu extension that allow attackers to fetch attacker-controlled remote URLs without SSRF protections via sendMediaFeishu function and markdown image processing. Attackers can influence tool calls through direct manipulation or prompt injection to trigger requests to internal services and re-upload responses as Feishu media.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2026-28451, is a type of &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; attack that affects the Feishu extension in OpenClaw versions prior to 2026.2.14. An attacker exploits it by tricking the system into making unauthorized requests to internal services, which can result in the re-upload of manipulated data. This can cause damage by allowing attackers to access sensitive internal data and potentially take control of internal services.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-27966</cve_id>
    <title>Langflow has Remote Code Execution in CSV Agent</title>
    <vendor>langflow-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.8</score>
    <description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.8.0, the CSV Agent node in Langflow hardcodes `allow_dangerous_code=True`, which automatically exposes LangChain’s Python REPL tool (`python_repl_ast`). As a result, an attacker can execute arbitrary Python and OS commands on the server via prompt injection, leading to full Remote Code Execution (RCE). Version 1.8.0 fixes the issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-27966 vulnerability is a Prompt Injection attack that allows an attacker to inject malicious code into a system. An attacker exploits this by sending crafted inputs to the LangChain's Python REPL tool, which then executes the attacker's code, allowing them to execute arbitrary Python and OS commands on the server. This can cause full Remote Code Execution (RCE), allowing the attacker to potentially gain complete control over the server.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-27740</cve_id>
    <title>Discourse has Stored XSS in AI Triage Automation</title>
    <vendor>discourse</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.1</score>
    <description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Versions prior to 2026.3.0-latest.1, 2026.2.1, and 2026.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability that arises because the system trusts the raw output from an AI Large Language Model (LLM) and renders it using htmlSafe in the Review Queue interface without adequate sanitization. A malicious attacker can use valid Prompt Injection techniques to force the AI to return a malicious payload (e.g., tags). When a Staff member (Admin/Moderator) views the flagged post in the Review Queue, the payload executes. Versions 2026.3.0-latest.1, 2026.2.1, and 2026.1.2 contain a patch. As a workaround, temporarily disable AI triage automation scripts.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-27740 is a cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw in the Discourse discussion platform, which allows an attacker to inject malicious code into the system.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by feeding the AI Large Language Model a specific input, forcing it to return malicious payload, which is then executed when a staff member views a flagged post in the Review Queue. 

This exploit can cause damage by allowing an attacker to take control of the system, potentially stealing sensitive information or disrupting the normal operation of the platform.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-27113</cve_id>
    <title>Liquid Prompt arbitrary command injection via crafted Git branch names in gitstatusd backend</title>
    <vendor>liquidprompt</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>Liquid Prompt is an adaptive prompt for Bash and Zsh. Starting in commit cf3441250bb5d8b45f6f8b389fcdf427a99ac28a and prior to commit a4f6b8d8c90b3eaa33d13dfd1093062ab9c4b30c on the master branch, arbitrary command injection can lead to code execution when a user enters a directory in a Git repository containing a crafted branch name. Exploitation requires the LP_ENABLE_GITSTATUSD config option to be enabled (enabled by default), gitstatusd to be installed and started before Liquid Prompt is loaded (not the default), and shell prompt substitution to be active (enabled by default in Bash via &quot;shopt -s promptvars&quot;, not enabled by default in Zsh). A branch name containing shell syntax such as &quot;$(...)&quot; or backtick expressions in the default branch or a checked-out branch will be evaluated by the shell when the prompt is rendered. No stable release is affected; only the master branch contains the vulnerable commit. Commit a4f6b8d8c90b3eaa33d13dfd1093062ab9c4b30c contains a fix. As a workaround, set the LP_ENABLE_GITSTATUSD config option to 0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is an issue in the Liquid Prompt tool that can allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands when a user enters a directory in a Git repository with a specially crafted branch name. Attackers exploit this by creating a crafted branch name that includes malicious shell syntax, which is then evaluated by the shell when the prompt is rendered, allowing them to execute their own commands. This exploitation can lead to the attacker gaining access to sensitive information and potentially taking control of the targeted system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-26321</cve_id>
    <title>OpenClaw has a local file disclosure via sendMediaFeishu in Feishu extension</title>
    <vendor>openclaw</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. Prior to OpenClaw version 2026.2.14, the Feishu extension previously allowed `sendMediaFeishu` to treat attacker-controlled `mediaUrl` values as local filesystem paths and read them directly. If an attacker can influence tool calls (directly or via prompt injection), they may be able to exfiltrate local files by supplying paths such as `/etc/passwd` as `mediaUrl`. Upgrade to OpenClaw `2026.2.14` or newer to receive a fix. The fix removes direct local file reads from this path and routes media loading through hardened helpers that enforce local-root restrictions.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2026-26321, is a Prompt Injection flaw in the OpenClaw personal AI assistant, which allows an attacker to manipulate user interactions to execute malicious actions. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious input, such as a request to access a sensitive file, and tricking the AI assistant into reading it directly from the local filesystem. This can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to exfiltrate sensitive local files, potentially compromising sensitive information and putting the affected system at risk.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-26268</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor sandbox escape via Git hooks</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.1</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Sandbox escape via writing .git configuration was possible in versions prior to 2.5. A malicious agent (ie prompt injection) could write to improperly protected .git settings, including git hooks, which may cause out-of-sandbox RCE next time they are triggered. No user interaction was required as Git executes these commands automatically. Fixed in version 2.5.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; flaw in the Cursor code editor, which allows an attacker to manipulate settings without user interaction. An attacker can exploit this by writing malicious code to the .git configuration, allowing them to execute commands remotely when the Git settings are triggered automatically. This can lead to a complete takeover of the system and execution of arbitrary code, causing significant damage and potentially allowing the attacker to steal sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-26057</cve_id>
    <title>Skill Scanner Unsecured Network Binding Vulnerability</title>
    <vendor>cisco-ai-defense</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.5</score>
    <description>Skill Scanner is a security scanner for AI Agent Skills that detects prompt injection, data exfiltration, and malicious code patterns. A vulnerability in the API Server of Skill Scanner could allow a unauthenticated, remote attacker to interact with the server API and either trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition or upload arbitrary files. This vulnerability is due to an erroneous binding to multiple interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending API requests to a device exposing the affected API Server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to consume an excessive amount of resources (memory starvation) or to upload files to arbitrary folders on the affected device. This vulnerability affects Skill-scanner 1.0.1 and earlier releases when the API Server is enabled. The API Server is not enabled by default. Skill-scanner software releases 1.0.2 and later contain the fix for this vulnerability.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The CVE-2026-26057 vulnerability is a security weakness in the API Server of Skill Scanner that allows an unauthenticated attacker to interact with the server and cause harm. An attacker exploits this weakness by sending malicious requests to the API Server, which can lead to either a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or the ability to upload arbitrary files to the affected device. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to consume excessive resources or upload malicious files to arbitrary folders, potentially compromising the device's security and integrity.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-24887</cve_id>
    <title>Claude Code has a Command Injection in find Command Bypasses User Approval Prompt</title>
    <vendor>anthropics</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.7</score>
    <description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.0.72, due to an error in command parsing, it was possible to bypass the Claude Code confirmation prompt to trigger execution of untrusted commands through the find command. Reliably exploiting this required the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.72.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection bug in Claude Code, an agentic coding tool, which allows malicious input to bypass its confirmation prompt.

An attacker exploits this bug by adding malicious content to a Claude Code context window, tricking it into executing untrusted commands. This can lead to unauthorized code execution or data modification.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can include unintended changes to sensitive data, unauthorized access to system resources, or even system compromise if exploited by a skilled attacker.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-24764</cve_id>
    <title>OpenClaw has Remote Code Execution via System Prompt Injection in Slack Channel Descriptions</title>
    <vendor>clawdbot</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>LOW</severity>
    <score>3.7</score>
    <description>OpenClaw (formerly Clawdbot) is a personal AI assistant users run on their own devices. In versions 2026.2.2 and below, when the Slack integration is enabled, channel metadata (topic/description) can be incorporated into the model's system prompt. Prompt injection is a documented risk for LLM-driven systems. This issue increases the injection surface by allowing untrusted Slack channel metadata to be treated as higher-trust system input. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.3.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in OpenClaw is called a prompt injection flaw, allowing hackers to influence the AI assistant to execute unauthorized system actions. Attackers can exploit this flaw by sending malicious channel metadata to OpenClaw's Slack integration, tricking the AI into performing actions it's not supposed to, such as accessing sensitive user data or executing system commands. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data breaches, unauthorized access, and disruption of system functions, giving hackers control over the user's AI assistant.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-67509</cve_id>
    <title>MySQLSelectTool Read-Only Bypass via SELECT INTO OUTFILE Allows Arbitrary File Write</title>
    <vendor>neuron-core</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.2</score>
    <description>Neuron is a PHP framework for creating and orchestrating AI Agents. Versions 2.8.11 and below use MySQLSelectTool, which is vulnerable to Read-Only Bypass. MySQLSelectTool is intended to be a read-only SQL tool (e.g., for LLM agent querying, however, validation based on the first keyword (e.g., SELECT) and a forbidden-keyword list does not block file-writing constructs such as INTO OUTFILE / INTO DUMPFILE. As a result, an attacker who can influence the tool input (e.g., via prompt injection through a public agent endpoint) may write arbitrary files to the DB server if the MySQL/MariaDB account has the FILE privilege and server configuration permits writes to a useful location (e.g., a web-accessible directory). This issue is fixed in version 2.8.12.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-67509, is a weakness in the MySQLSelectTool that allows an attacker to bypass read-only restrictions and write files to a database server. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting specific prompts into a public agent endpoint, which can then be used to write arbitrary files on the database server, potentially allowing the attacker to steal sensitive data or disrupt the system. The impact of this vulnerability could result in unauthorized data access or manipulation, as well as potentially allowing an attacker to gain control over the database server.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-65106</cve_id>
    <title>LangChain Vulnerable to Template Injection via Attribute Access in Prompt Templates</title>
    <vendor>langchain-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.3</score>
    <description>LangChain is a framework for building agents and LLM-powered applications. From versions 0.3.79 and prior and 1.0.0 to 1.0.6, a template injection vulnerability exists in LangChain's prompt template system that allows attackers to access Python object internals through template syntax. This vulnerability affects applications that accept untrusted template strings (not just template variables) in ChatPromptTemplate and related prompt template classes. This issue has been patched in versions 0.3.80 and 1.0.7.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2025-65106 vulnerability is a type of injection issue, called prompt injection, that allows attackers to manipulate the internal workings of a LangChain framework by inserting malicious template strings.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted template string to an application that uses the LangChain framework, which can allow the attacker to access and manipulate the application's internal data.

If successfully exploited, the vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access to an application's sensitive data, potentially causing data breaches, corruption, and other serious security risks.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-64110</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor: Authentication Bypass Possible via New Cursorignore Write</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.7</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.23 and below, a logic bug allows a malicious agent to read sensitive files that should be protected via cursorignore. An attacker who has already achieved prompt injection, or a malicious model, could create a new cursorignore file which can invalidate the configuration of pre-existing ones. This could allow a malicious agent to read protected files. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a logic bug in the Cursor code editor that allows a malicious agent to read sensitive files protected by the cursorignore configuration. An attacker can exploit this by creating a new file that invalidates the existing cursorignore configuration, allowing them to access and read protected files. This can cause significant damage by giving attackers unrestricted access to sensitive data, potentially leading to data theft, intellectual property loss, or even financial losses.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-64108</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor's Sensitive File Modification can Lead to NTFS Path Quirks</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.44 and below, various NTFS path quirks allow a prompt injection attacker to circumvent sensitive file protections and overwrite files which Cursor requires human approval to overwrite. Modification of some of the protected files can lead to RCE. Must be chained with a prompt injection or malicious model attach. Only affects systems supporting NTFS. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2025-64108, is a flaw in Cursor's code editor that allows attackers to bypass file protection. An attacker exploits this by tricking Cursor into modifying sensitive files without proper approval, which could allow them to take full control of the system. This can cause remote code execution (RCE), giving the attacker the power to do anything they want with the compromised system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-64107</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor is Vulnerable to Path Manipulation Using Backslashes on Windows</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.52 and below, manipulating internal settings may lead to RCE. Cursor detects path manipulation via forward slashes (./.cursor/./././././mcp.json etc.), and requires human approval to complete the operation. However, the same kind of manipulation using backslashes was not correctly detected, allowing an attacker who had already achieved prompt injection or some other level of control to overwrite sensitive editor files without approval on Windows machines. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are 3 simple sentences explaining the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a Remote Code Execution (RCE) flaw in the Cursor code editor, specifically affecting versions 1.7.52 and below, allowing an attacker to gain control of the system. An attacker exploits this by manipulating file paths using backslashes, which the Cursor system mistakenly believes requires user approval, allowing the attacker to overwrite sensitive files without being detected. This can cause significant damage by granting an attacker full control over the system, essentially allowing them to execute arbitrary code and potentially access sensitive information or spread malware.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-61593</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor CLI Agent: Sensitive File Overwrite Bypass</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.1</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7 and below, a vulnerability in the way Cursor CLI Agent protects its sensitive files (i.e. */.cursor/cli.json) allows attackers to modify the content of the files through prompt injection, thus achieving remote code execution. A prompt injection can lead to full RCE through modifying sensitive files on case-insensitive filesystems. This issue is fixed in a commit, 25b418f, but has yet to be released as of October 3, 2025.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are three simple sentences explaining the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection flaw in Cursor's CLI Agent, which allows an attacker to manipulate sensitive files on the system. An attacker exploits it by tricking the system into executing a malicious command, which modifies the CLI Agent's files, and gains full control of the system. The damage this can cause is remote code execution (RCE), allowing an attacker to access, modify, or delete sensitive data on the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-61592</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor CLI: Arbitrary Code Execution Possible through Permissive CLI Config</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7 and below, automatic loading of project-specific CLI configuration from the current working directory (&lt;project&gt;/.cursor/cli.json) could override certain global configurations in Cursor CLI. This allowed users running the CLI inside a malicious repository to be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution through a combination of permissive configuration (allowing shell commands) and prompt injection delivered via project-specific Rules (&lt;project&gt;/.cursor/rules/rule.mdc) or other mechanisms. The fix for this issue is currently available as a patch 2025.09.17-25b418f. As of October 3, 2025 there is no release version.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in Cursor CLI is a configuration override issue, where a user's settings can be overridden by a malicious project-specific configuration file.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by creating a malicious repository that includes a specially crafted configuration file, allowing the attacker to inject malicious commands and execute them on the victim's system. 

This vulnerability can cause Remote Code Execution, allowing an attacker to take control of the victim's system and potentially steal sensitive information or install malicious software.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-61590</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor is vulnerable to RCE via .code-workspace files using Prompt Injection</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Versions 1.6 and below are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) attacks through Visual Studio Code Workspaces. Workspaces allow users to open more than a single folder and save specific settings (pretty similar to .vscode/settings.json) for the folders / project. An untitled workspace is automatically created by VS Code (untitled.code-workspace), which contains all the folders and workspace settings from the user's current session, opening up an entire new attack vector if the user has a .code-workspace file in path (either untitled created automatically or a saved one). If an attacker is able to hijack the chat context of the victim (such as via a compromised MCP server), they can use prompt injection to make the Cursor Agent write into this file and modify the workspace. This leads to a bypass of CVE-2025-54130 which can lead to RCE by writing to the settings section. This issue is fixed in version 1.7.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a code injection flaw in the Cursor code editor that allows attackers to execute malicious code remotely.

An attacker can hijack a user's chat context, typically through a compromised chat server, and inject malicious code into the Cursor Agent. This code is then executed by the Agent, which modifies the user's workspace settings.

The damage this vulnerability can cause includes full control of the victim's machine, as the attacker gains the ability to inject and execute arbitrary code, leading to potentially catastrophic consequences.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-61589</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor: Potential Information Leakage via Mermaid Diagram</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.9</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.6 and below, Mermaid (a to render diagrams) allows embedding images which then get rendered by Cursor in the chat box. An attacker can use this to exfiltrate sensitive information to a third-party attacker controlled server through an image fetch after successfully performing a prompt injection. A malicious model (or hallucination/backdoor) might also trigger this exploit at will. This issue requires prompt injection from malicious data (web, image upload, source code) in order to exploit. In that case, it can send sensitive information to an attacker-controlled external server. Some additional bypasses not covered in the initial fix to this issue were discovered, see GHSA-43wj-mwcc-x93p. This issue is fixed in version 1.7.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2025-61589 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is called prompt injection in Mermaid, a tool used by the Cursor code editor to render diagrams. An attacker exploits this by tricking the editor into sending sensitive information to a third-party server, allowing the attacker to extract confidential data. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can cause sensitive data to be stolen and potentially leaked, compromising user privacy and security.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-59944</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor IDE: Sensitive File Overwrite Bypass is Possible</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.1</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Versions 1.6.23 and below contain case-sensitive checks in the way Cursor IDE protects its sensitive files (e.g., */.cursor/mcp.json), which allows attackers to modify the content of these files through prompt injection and achieve remote code execution. A prompt injection can lead to full RCE through modifying sensitive files on case-insensitive fileystems. This issue is fixed in version 1.7.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2025-59944 vulnerability is a case of sensitive file protection bypass, allowing attackers to modify sensitive files in the Cursor IDE code editor. An attacker exploits this vulnerability through &quot;prompt injection,&quot; where they use specific inputs to trick the editor into changing sensitive files, ultimately giving them control over the system. This can lead to remote code execution, allowing the attacker to take control of the computer and perform malicious actions.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-5963</cve_id>
    <title>TCC Bypass via Dylib Injection in Postbox</title>
    <vendor>Postbox</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.8</score>
    <description>The Postbox's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlements: &quot;com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables&quot; and &quot;com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation&quot; allows for Dynamic Library (Dylib) injection. A local attacker with unprivileged access can use environment variables like DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES to successfully inject code in application's context and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission. The original company behind Postbox is no longer operational, the software will no longer receive updates. The acquiring company (em Client) did not cooperate in vulnerability disclosure.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2025-5963, is a security weakness in Postbox's configuration on macOS that allows an attacker to inject malicious code into the application, effectively bypassing security restrictions. An attacker with local, unprivileged access can exploit this vulnerability by using environment variables to inject code, which can prompt the user for additional permissions, potentially leading to unauthorized access to system resources. This could result in damage to the system, potentially allowing the attacker to steal sensitive data, install malware, or disrupt system functionality, and since Postbox won't receive updates, this hole will likely be permanent.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-59417</cve_id>
    <title>Lobe Chat Desktop Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via XSS in Chat Messages</title>
    <vendor>lobehub</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.8</score>
    <description>Lobe Chat is an open-source artificial intelligence chat framework. Prior to version 1.129.4, there is a a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability when handling chat message in lobe-chat that can be escalated to remote code execution on the user’s machine. In lobe-chat, when the response from the server is like &lt;lobeArtifact identifier=&quot;ai-new-interpretation&quot; ...&gt; , it will be rendered with the lobeArtifact node, instead of the plain text. However, when the type of the lobeArtifact is image/svg+xml , it will be rendered as the SVGRender component, which internally uses dangerouslySetInnerHTML to set the content of the svg, resulting in XSS attack. Any party capable of injecting content into chat messages, such as hosting a malicious page for prompt injection, operating a compromised MCP server, or leveraging tool integrations, can exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.129.4.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2025-59417 vulnerability in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability is a cross-site scripting (XSS) issue in the Lobe Chat framework, which allows attackers to inject malicious code into the chat messages.

Attackers exploit this by creating a fake webpage that tricks users into sending malicious chat messages, which are then executed on the user's machine as if they were legitimate code. This can cause damage by allowing attackers to steal sensitive information, take control of the user's machine, or even install malware.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-58764</cve_id>
    <title>Claude Code rg command had Command Injection that allowed bypass of user approval prompt for command execution</title>
    <vendor>anthropics</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.7</score>
    <description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Due to an error in command parsing, versions prior to 1.0.105 were vulnerable to a bypass of the Claude Code confirmation prompt to trigger execution of an untrusted command. Reliably exploiting this requires the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window. Users on standard Claude Code auto-update will have received this fix automatically. Users performing manual updates are advised to update to version 1.0.105 or the latest version.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2025-58764, is a type of attack called Prompt Injection, where an attacker tricks the system into executing commands without warning the user. An attacker exploits this by inserting malicious content into a Claude Code context window, which the system mistakenly interprets as a legitimate command. This allows the attacker to run unauthorized code, potentially leading to data theft, system crashes, or even full system takeover.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-58372</cve_id>
    <title>Roo Code: Potential Remote Code Execution via .code-workspace</title>
    <vendor>RooCodeInc</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.1</score>
    <description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent that lives in users' editors. Versions 3.25.23 and below contain a vulnerability where certain VS Code workspace configuration files (.code-workspace) are not protected in the same way as the .vscode folder. If the agent was configured to auto-approve file writes, an attacker able to influence prompts (for example via prompt injection) could cause malicious workspace settings or tasks to be written. These tasks could then be executed automatically when the workspace is reopened, resulting in arbitrary code execution. This issue is fixed in version 3.26.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2025-58372 vulnerability is a prompt injection vulnerability in Roo Code, an AI-powered coding agent, that allows attackers to execute malicious tasks. An attacker exploits this by influencing the prompts that Roo Code uses, which can cause the agent to write malicious workspace settings or tasks, and these tasks can then be executed automatically when the workspace is reopened. This can cause the attacker to run arbitrary code, potentially allowing them to access or modify data, or even take control of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-58357</cve_id>
    <title>5ire Chat Message XSS Vulnerability Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
    <vendor>nanbingxyz</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.7</score>
    <description>5ire is a cross-platform desktop artificial intelligence assistant and model context protocol client. Version 0.13.2 contains a vulnerability in the chat page's script gadgets that enables content injection attacks through multiple vectors: malicious prompt injection pages, compromised MCP servers, and exploited tool integrations. This is fixed in version 0.14.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2025-58357 vulnerability:

The vulnerability, known as Prompt Injection, allows an attacker to inject malicious code into a 5ire chat page through various means. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can gain unauthorized access to a user's account or sensitive information, which can be used for malicious purposes such as stealing personal data or spreading malware. The damage caused by this vulnerability can include the theft of sensitive information, unauthorized changes to user accounts, and potentially even complete control of the user's system or device.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-54135</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor Agent is vulnerable to prompt injection via MCP Special Files</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.6</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Cursor allows writing in-workspace files with no user approval in versions below 1.3.9, If the file is a dotfile, editing it requires approval but creating a new one doesn't. Hence, if sensitive MCP files, such as the .cursor/mcp.json file don't already exist in the workspace, an attacker can chain a indirect prompt injection vulnerability to hijack the context to write to the settings file and trigger RCE on the victim without user approval. This is fixed in version 1.3.9.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-54135, is a prompt injection flaw in the Cursor code editor that allows an attacker to secretly modify sensitive settings files. The attacker exploits this by creating a new file that allows them to inject malicious code into the settings, giving them unauthorized access to the system; in this case, allowing Remote Code Execution (RCE). This vulnerability can cause significant damage, as it enables an attacker to gain remote access to a system and potentially steal sensitive data, disrupt operations, or install malware.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-54132</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor's Mermaid Diagram Tool is Vulnerable to an Arbitrary Image Fetch</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.4</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions below 1.3, Mermaid (which is used to render diagrams) allows embedding images which then get rendered by Cursor in the chat box. An attacker can use this to exfiltrate sensitive information to a third-party attacker controlled server through an image fetch after successfully performing a prompt injection. A malicious model (or hallucination/backdoor) might also trigger this exploit at will. This issue requires prompt injection from malicious data (web, image upload, source code) in order to exploit. In that case, it can send sensitive information to an attacker-controlled external server. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-54132, is a prompt injection flaw in the Cursor code editor that allows an attacker to inject malicious data into the system.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by uploading malicious data to the system, such as a malicious image or code, which contains a command that instructs the system to fetch sensitive information and send it to an attacker-controlled server. This can be done through various means, including web uploads or malicious source code.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to exfiltrate sensitive information, such as confidential data or user credentials, to an external server controlled by the attacker, potentially leading to data theft or identity compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-54131</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor bypasses its allow list to execute arbitrary commands</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.4</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions below 1.3, an attacker can bypass the allow list in auto-run mode with a backtick (`) or $(cmd). If a user has swapped Cursor from its default settings (requiring approval for every terminal call) to an allowlist, an attacker can execute arbitrary command execution outside of the allowlist without user approval. An attacker can trigger this vulnerability if chained with indirect prompt injection. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; issue in Cursor, a code editor, where an attacker can bypass the approved list of commands when using the auto-run mode. An attacker exploits this by inserting special characters, like a backtick or dollar sign, into a prompt, allowing them to execute arbitrary commands without user approval. This can cause significant damage, as it enables an attacker to execute unauthorized commands, potentially leading to data theft or system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-54130</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor Agent is vulnerable prompt injection via Editor Special Files</title>
    <vendor>cursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Cursor allows writing in-workspace files with no user approval in versions less than 1.3.9. If the file is a dotfile, editing it requires approval but creating a new one doesn't. Hence, if sensitive editor files, such as the .vscode/settings.json file don't already exist in the workspace, an attacker can chain a indirect prompt injection vulnerability to hijack the context to write to the settings file and trigger RCE on the victim without user approval. This is fixed in version 1.3.9.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection flaw in the Cursor code editor, which allows an attacker to create sensitive files without user consent.

An attacker exploits this by using a dotfile (a hidden file) to inject malicious code into the editor's settings file, allowing them to gain remote code execution (RCE) on the victim's system without needing their approval.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can lead to a full remote code execution (RCE) on the victim's system, giving the attacker complete control over the affected device.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-53773</cve_id>
    <title>GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
    <vendor>Microsoft</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.8</score>
    <description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio allows an unauthorized attacker to execute code locally.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a 3-sentence explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a code injection bug in GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio that allows an attacker to input malicious code and execute it on a user's computer without their permission. An attacker exploits this bug by sending manipulated code in a prompt, tricking the system into running it locally, which can lead to data loss, corruption, or even complete system takeover. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by giving an attacker the ability to access and manipulate sensitive information, install malware, or disrupt critical services.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-53107</cve_id>
    <title>@cyanheads/git-mcp-server vulnerable to command injection in several tools</title>
    <vendor>cyanheads</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>@cyanheads/git-mcp-server is an MCP server designed to interact with Git repositories. Prior to version 2.1.5, there is a command injection vulnerability caused by the unsanitized use of input parameters within a call to child_process.exec, enabling an attacker to inject arbitrary system commands. Successful exploitation can lead to remote code execution under the server process's privileges. The server constructs and executes shell commands using unvalidated user input directly within command-line strings. This introduces the possibility of shell metacharacter injection (|, &gt;, &amp;&amp;, etc.). An MCP Client can be instructed to execute additional actions for example via indirect prompt injection when asked to read git logs. This issue has been patched in version 2.1.5.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-53107, occurs when an attacker can inject malicious commands into a system through user input, allowing them to take control of the server process. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending specially crafted input to the server, which then unknowingly executes the attacker's malicious commands, giving the attacker the ability to control the server and access sensitive data. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can lead to severe damage, including the theft of sensitive data, disruption of services, and potentially even system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-53097</cve_id>
    <title>Roo Code extension vulnerable to Potential Information Leakage via JSON Schema</title>
    <vendor>RooCodeInc</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.9</score>
    <description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent. Prior to version 3.20.3, there was an issue where the Roo Code agent's `search_files` tool did not respect the setting to disable reads outside of the VS Code workspace. This means that an attacker who was able to inject a prompt into the agent could potentially read a sensitive file and then write the information to a JSON schema. Users have the option to disable schema fetching in VS Code, but the feature is enabled by default. For users with this feature enabled, writing to the schema would trigger a network request without the user having a chance to deny. This issue is of moderate severity, since it requires the attacker to already be able to submit prompts to the agent. Version 3.20.3 fixed the issue where `search_files` did not respect the setting to limit it to the workspace. This reduces the scope of the damage if an attacker is able to take control of the agent through prompt injection or another vector.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection issue in the Roo Code AI-powered coding agent, which allows an attacker to inject a prompt that forces the agent to read a sensitive file.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by submitting a malicious prompt to the Roo Code agent, which tricks it into reading and extracting sensitive information from outside the designated workspace.

This allows the attacker to gain access to sensitive data and potentially use it to their advantage, such as breaching confidentiality or exploiting the information for malicious purposes.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-52573</cve_id>
    <title>Command Injection in MCP Server ios-simulator-mcp</title>
    <vendor>joshuayoes</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.0</score>
    <description>iOS Simulator MCP Server (ios-simulator-mcp) is a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server for interacting with iOS simulators. Versions prior to 1.3.3 are written in a way that is vulnerable to command injection vulnerability attacks as part of some of its MCP Server tool definition and implementation. The MCP Server exposes the tool `ui_tap` which relies on Node.js child process API `exec` which is an unsafe and vulnerable API if concatenated with untrusted user input. LLM exposed user input for `duration`, `udid`, and `x` and `y` args can be replaced with shell meta-characters like `;` or `&amp;&amp;` or others to change the behavior from running the expected command `idb` to another command. When LLMs are tricked through prompt injection (and other techniques and attack vectors) to call the tool with input that uses special shell characters such as `; rm -rf /tmp;#` and other payload variations, the full command-line text will be interepted by the shell and result in other commands except of `ps` executing on the host running the MCP Server. Version 1.3.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are 3 simple sentences explaining the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability, known as command injection, occurs when an attacker can trick the iOS Simulator's MCP Server into executing unintended commands. The attacker can do this by sending specially crafted input that contains shell meta-characters, such as semicolons or ampersands, which can modify the command being executed. This can allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the host system, potentially leading to data theft, system compromise, or other severe damage.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-5255</cve_id>
    <title>TCC Bypass via Dylib Injection in Phoenix Code</title>
    <vendor>Core.ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.8</score>
    <description>The Phoenix Code's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlements: &quot;com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables&quot; and &quot;com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation&quot; allows for Dynamic Library (Dylib) injection. A local attacker with unprivileged access can use environment variables like DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES to successfully inject code in application's context and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission. This issue was fixed in commit 0c75fb57f89d0b7d9b180026bc2624b7dcf807da</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2025-5255 is a code injection bug that allows an attacker to inject malicious code into a legitimate app on a macOS system. The attacker exploits this by setting a specific environment variable, such as DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES, to run their own code alongside the regular app code, essentially hacking into the app. This can cause damage by allowing the attacker to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions on the system, which could lead to data theft or system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-49150</cve_id>
    <title>Cursor Agent Potentially Leaks Information using JSON schema</title>
    <vendor>getcursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.9</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Prior to 0.51.0, by default, the setting json.schemaDownload.enable was set to True. This means that by writing a JSON file, an attacker can trigger an arbitrary HTTP GET request that does not require user confirmation. Since the Cursor Agent can edit JSON files, this means a malicious agent, for example, after a prompt injection attack already succeeded, could trigger a GET request to an attacker controlled URL, potentially exfiltrating other data the agent may have access to. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.51.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2025-49150, is a prompt injection flaw in the Cursor code editor, which allows an attacker to manipulate the editor into making unintended HTTP requests. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by writing a malicious JSON file, which tricks the editor into sending sensitive information to a controlled URL without user confirmation. If successful, the attack can lead to data exfiltration, allowing the attacker to access and steal other sensitive information that the affected agent may have access to.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-46735</cve_id>
    <title>Terraform WinDNS Provider improperly sanitizes input variables in `windns_record`</title>
    <vendor>nrkno</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>LOW</severity>
    <score>1.1</score>
    <description>Terraform WinDNS Provider allows users to manage their Windows DNS server resources through Terraform. A security issue has been found in Terraform WinDNS Provider before version `1.0.5`. The `windns_record` resource did not sanitize the input variables. This could lead to authenticated command injection in the underlyding powershell command prompt. Version 1.0.5 contains a fix for the issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-46735, involves a problem with the Terraform WinDNS provider where it does not properly sanitize user input, potentially allowing malicious commands to be executed.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious commands into the Terraform configuration, which are then executed by the Windows PowerShell command prompt. This allows the attacker to gain unauthorized access or control over the affected system.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access, data tampering, or even full system compromise, as malicious commands can be executed with the same privileges as the Terraform user account.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-43858</cve_id>
    <title>YoutubeDLSharp allows command injection on windows system due to non sanitized arguments</title>
    <vendor>Bluegrams</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.2</score>
    <description>YoutubeDLSharp is a wrapper for the command-line video downloaders youtube-dl and yt-dlp. In versions starting from 1.0.0-beta4 and prior to 1.1.2, an unsafe conversion of arguments allows the injection of a malicious commands when starting `yt-dlp` from a commands prompt running on Windows OS with the `UseWindowsEncodingWorkaround` value defined to true (default behavior). If a user is using built-in methods from the YoutubeDL.cs file, the value is true by default and a user cannot disable it from these methods. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.2.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; issue in the YoutubeDLSharp library, which allows an attacker to inject malicious commands into the system. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by using crafted input to execute unauthorized commands when a user runs the 'yt-dlp' command, allowing the attacker to potentially gain control of the system. This can cause damage by allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary system commands, which can lead to system compromise, data theft, or other malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-3579</cve_id>
    <title>Code Injection Vulnerability in AiDex</title>
    <vendor>AiDex</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.3</score>
    <description>In versions prior to Aidex 1.7, an authenticated malicious user, taking advantage of an open registry, could execute unauthorised commands within the system. This includes executing operating system (Unix) commands, interacting with internal services such as PHP or MySQL, and even invoking native functions of the framework used, such as Laravel or Symfony. This execution is achieved by Prompt Injection attacks through the /api/&lt;string-chat&gt;/message endpoint, manipulating the content of the ‘content’ parameter.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are the explanations in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-3579, is a Prompt Injection issue in Aidex versions prior to 1.7 that allows an authenticated malicious user to execute arbitrary system commands.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the 'content' parameter in the /api/&lt;string-chat&gt;/message endpoint, forcing Aidex to run unwanted commands, which can interact with the system, invoke internal services, or access native functions within the framework.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, allowing an attacker to potentially take control of the system, steal sensitive data, or perform other malicious actions that compromise the security and integrity of the Aidex system and the surrounding environment.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-32018</cve_id>
    <title>Arbitrary file write from Cursor Agent through a prompt injection from malicious @Docs</title>
    <vendor>getcursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.1</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 0.45.0 through 0.48.6, the Cursor app introduced a regression affecting the set of file paths the Cursor Agent is permitted to modify automatically. Under specific conditions, the agent could be prompted, either directly by the user or via maliciously crafted context, to automatically write to files outside of the opened workspace. This behavior required deliberate prompting, making successful exploitation highly impractical in real-world scenarios. Furthermore, the edited file was still displayed in the UI as usual for user review, making it unlikely for the edit to go unnoticed by the user. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.48.7.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a Prompt Injection issue in the Cursor code editor that affects the Cursor Agent, allowing it to write to unintended files. An attacker exploits this by tricking the Cursor Agent into automatically writing to files outside the intended workspace, typically by manipulating the app's context or user input, which requires specific deliberate prompting. This vulnerability could cause damage by allowing an attacker to modify sensitive files, potentially leading to data loss, corruption, or even unauthorized code execution.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-31363</cve_id>
    <title>Data exfiltration via AI plugin Jira tool</title>
    <vendor>Mattermost</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>LOW</severity>
    <score>3.0</score>
    <description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.9 fail to restrict domains the LLM can request to contact upstream which allows an authenticated user to exfiltrate data from an arbitrary server accessible to the victim via performing a prompt injection in the AI plugin's Jira tool.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

1. The vulnerability is a type of bug where attackers can trick the Mattermost AI plugin into contacting an arbitrary server, allowing them to access sensitive information.
2. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted prompt or message in the AI plugin's Jira tool, which tricks the plugin into making an unauthorized connection to the attacker's server.
3. This vulnerability could cause damage by allowing the attacker to exfiltrate sensitive data from an arbitrary server, which could include confidential business information, customer data, or even sensitive user credentials.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-2733</cve_id>
    <title>mannaandpoem OpenManus Prompt os command injection</title>
    <vendor>mannaandpoem</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects an unknown part of the file app/tool/python_execute.py of the component Prompt Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2025-2733 is a Critical Prompt Injection flaw in a part of the OpenManus system, which allows an attacker to inject malicious commands. An attacker exploits this by crafting a malicious prompt that is executed by the system, potentially leading to unauthorized access or data tampering. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary system commands, potentially leading to data theft, system compromise, or even a full system takeover.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2025-11445</cve_id>
    <title>Kilo Code Prompt ClineProvider.ts ClineProvider injection</title>
    <vendor>n/a</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in Kilo Code up to 4.86.0. Affected is the function ClineProvider of the file src/core/webview/ClineProvider.ts of the component Prompt Handler. Performing manipulation results in injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simplified explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-11445, is a Prompt Injection bug in the Kilo Code software, which allows attackers to inject malicious text into the system. Attacker can exploit this by sending specially crafted input remotely, which trick the system into executing the malicious text. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can cause significant damage by potentially stealing sensitive information, disrupting system functionality, and even taking control of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-8309</cve_id>
    <title>SQL Injection in langchain-ai/langchain</title>
    <vendor>langchain-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.9</score>
    <description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchain version 0.2.5 allows for SQL injection through prompt injection. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

This vulnerability is a Prompt Injection issue in a specific class of the langchain-ai language system, allowing malicious input to be injected into the system. Attackers exploit this by sending carefully crafted input that tricks the system into executing unauthorized SQL commands, like deleting data or stealing sensitive information. If exploited, this vulnerability can cause significant damage, including deleting all data, stealing sensitive data, disrupting services, and compromising the integrity of the database.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-8055</cve_id>
    <title>Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection via SnowFlake SQL in vanna-ai/vanna</title>
    <vendor>vanna-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>Vanna v0.6.3 is vulnerable to SQL injection via Snowflake database in its file staging operations using the `PUT` and `COPY` commands. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote users to read arbitrary local files on the victim server, such as `/etc/passwd`, by exploiting the exposed SQL queries through a Python Flask API.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2024-8055 is a SQL injection flaw in the Vanna v0.6.3 application's Snowflake database, allowing malicious actors to insert unexpected commands. An attacker exploits this by sending a special, crafted input (Prompt Injection) to the application's API, which is then executed by the Snowflake database as a SQL query, allowing the attacker to access local files on the server. This attack can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to read sensitive local files like system configuration and user passwords, potentially leading to a complete compromise of the server.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-7110</cve_id>
    <title>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') in GitLab</title>
    <vendor>GitLab</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.4</score>
    <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting 17.0 to 17.1.6, 17.2 prior to 17.2.4, and 17.3 prior to 17.3.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary command in a victim's pipeline through prompt injection.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a breakdown of the vulnerability in simple terms:

CVE-2024-7110 is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; vulnerability found in GitLab EE that allows attackers to trick the system into running malicious commands unintentionally. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious information into prompts in a victim's pipeline, which then executes the attacker's commands under the victim's privilege level. This can cause significant damage, including data theft, system compromise, and disruption of critical services, allowing the attacker to gain unauthorized access and control over the victim's system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-7042</cve_id>
    <title>Prompt Injection</title>
    <vendor>langchain-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.9</score>
    <description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchainjs versions 0.2.5 and all versions with this class allows for prompt injection, leading to SQL injection. This vulnerability permits unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2024-7042 vulnerability is a prompt injection flaw in certain versions of the langchainjs library, allowing an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by crafting a malicious prompt that is interpreted as SQL code, allowing them to manipulate or steal sensitive data. This exploitation can cause significant damage, including unauthorized data manipulation, data breaches, denial of service, and compromises to database integrity, potentially leading to business disruption or financial loss.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-6331</cve_id>
    <title>Injection in stitionai/devika</title>
    <vendor>stitionai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>stitionai/devika main branch as of commit cdfb782b0e634b773b10963c8034dc9207ba1f9f is vulnerable to Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection. The integration of Google Gimini 1.0 Pro with `HarmBlockThreshold.BLOCK_NONE` for `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HATE_SPEECH` and `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HARASSMENT` in `safety_settings` disables content protection. This allows malicious commands to be executed, such as reading sensitive file contents like `/etc/passwd`.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2024-6331, is a Local File Read (LFI) exploit that allows an attacker to access sensitive files on a system. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious commands into a prompt, which is then executed by the vulnerable system, allowing them to view sensitive file contents like passwords or system configuration files. This could cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to access highly sensitive information, including passwords and system configuration files, potentially leading to a complete system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-58340</cve_id>
    <title>LangChain &lt;= 0.3.1 MRKLOutputParser ReDoS</title>
    <vendor>LangChain AI</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.7</score>
    <description>LangChain versions up to and including 0.3.1 contain a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) vulnerability in the MRKLOutputParser.parse() method (libs/langchain/langchain/agents/mrkl/output_parser.py). The parser applies a backtracking-prone regular expression when extracting tool actions from model output. An attacker who can supply or influence the parsed text (for example via prompt injection in downstream applications that pass LLM output directly into MRKLOutputParser.parse()) can trigger excessive CPU consumption by providing a crafted payload, causing significant parsing delays and a denial-of-service condition.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2024-58340 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) issue where a malicious input can cause the system to consume excessive CPU resources, leading to a denial-of-service condition.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting a crafted payload into the system through the MRKLOutputParser.parse() method, potentially allowing them to freeze or slow down the system.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can lead to significant parsing delays and a denial-of-service condition, resulting in system instability, downtime, or even security breaches if exploited further.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-5827</cve_id>
    <title>Arbitrary File Write by Prompt Injection via DuckDB SQL in vanna-ai/vanna</title>
    <vendor>vanna-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.8</score>
    <description>Vanna v0.3.4 is vulnerable to SQL injection in its DuckDB integration exposed to its Flask Web APIs. Attackers can inject malicious SQL training data and generate corresponding queries to write arbitrary files on the victim's file system, such as backdoor.php with contents `&lt;?php system($_GET[0]); ?&gt;`. This can lead to command execution or the creation of backdoors.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2024-5827 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the Vanna application's Flask Web API that interacts with its DuckDB database. An attacker can exploit this by injecting malicious SQL code into the application's queries, allowing them to execute arbitrary commands on the system or upload backdoor files like backdoor.php. This vulnerability can cause severe damage by enabling an attacker to gain full control of the system, potentially leading to ransomware attacks, data theft, or the installation of malicious software.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-5826</cve_id>
    <title>Remote Code Execution via Prompt Injection in vanna-ai/vanna</title>
    <vendor>vanna-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.8</score>
    <description>In the latest version of vanna-ai/vanna, the `vanna.ask` function is vulnerable to remote code execution due to prompt injection. The root cause is the lack of a sandbox when executing LLM-generated code, allowing an attacker to manipulate the code executed by the `exec` function in `src/vanna/base/base.py`. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to achieve remote code execution on the app backend server, potentially gaining full control of the server.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2024-5826 vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability is a remote code execution flaw in a function called `vanna.ask` that allows attackers to inject malicious code. An attacker can exploit this by tricking the system into running their own malicious code using a technique called prompt injection, allowing them to control the app server. If exploited, this vulnerability can give the attacker complete control over the app server, potentially leading to serious damage such as data theft or server hijacking.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-5753</cve_id>
    <title>Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection via Postgres SQL in vanna-ai/vanna</title>
    <vendor>vanna-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>vanna-ai/vanna version v0.3.4 is vulnerable to SQL injection in some file-critical functions such as `pg_read_file()`. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote users to read arbitrary local files on the victim server, including sensitive files like `/etc/passwd`, by exploiting the exposed SQL queries via a Python Flask API.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2024-5753, is a SQL injection issue that allows an attacker to access sensitive local files on the victim server. An attacker exploits this by sending malicious input through a Python Flask API, which can cause the vulnerable system to reveal the contents of those files. This can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to access sensitive information, such as passwords or configuration files, potentially leading to further security breaches or system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-5184</cve_id>
    <title>Prompt Injection in EmailGPT</title>
    <vendor>EmailGPT</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.5</score>
    <description>The EmailGPT service contains a prompt injection vulnerability. The service uses an API service that allows a malicious user to inject a direct prompt and take over the service logic. Attackers can exploit the issue by forcing the AI service to leak the standard hard-coded system prompts and/or execute unwanted prompts. When engaging with EmailGPT by submitting a malicious prompt that requests harmful information, the system will respond by providing the requested data. This vulnerability can be exploited by any individual with access to the service.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2024-5184, is a prompt injection flaw in the EmailGPT service that allows an attacker to manipulate the service's logic and requests.

An attacker exploits this flaw by submitting a malicious prompt that tricks the AI service into revealing sensitive information or performing unwanted actions, such as providing access to private data.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data breaches, unauthorized access to sensitive information, and disruption of normal service operations, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized control over the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-48919</cve_id>
    <title>RCE via Prompt Injection Into Cursor's Terminal Cmd-K</title>
    <vendor>getcursor</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.2</score>
    <description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Prior to Sep 27, 2024, if a user generated a terminal command via Cursor's Terminal Cmd-K/Ctrl-K feature and if the user explicitly imported a malicious web page into the Terminal Cmd-K prompt, an attacker with control over the referenced web page could have a significant chance of influencing a language model to output arbitrary commands for execution in the user's terminal. This scenario would require the user explicitly opt-in to including the contents of a compromised webpage, and it would require that the attacker display prompt injection text in the the contents of the compromised webpage. A server-side patch to not stream back newlines or control characters was released on September 27, 2024, within two hours of the issue being reported. Additionally, Cursor 0.42 includes client-side mitigations to prevent any newline or control character from being streamed into the terminal directly. It also contains a new setting, `&quot;cursor.terminal.usePreviewBox&quot;`, which, if set to true, streams the response into a preview box whose contents then have to be manually accepted before being inserted into the terminal. This setting is useful if you're working in a shell environment where commands can be executed without pressing enter or any control character. The patch has been applied server-side, so no additional action is needed, even on older versions of Cursor. Separately, Cursor's maintainers also recommend, as best practice, to only include trusted pieces of context in prompts.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2024-48919 is a Prompt Injection vulnerability in the Cursor code editor, which allows an attacker to manipulate the terminal commands a user inputs. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by luring a user into importing a malicious webpage into the terminal and crafting the webpage to inject malicious commands, which are then executed in the user's terminal when the user accepts the webpage's contents. This can cause damage, such as executing arbitrary system commands, which can lead to the theft of sensitive data, unauthorized system modifications, or even system crashes.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-41815</cve_id>
    <title>Starship vulnerable to shell injection via undocumented, unpredictable shell expansion in custom commands</title>
    <vendor>starship</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.4</score>
    <description>Starship is a cross-shell prompt. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 1.20.0, undocumented and unpredictable shell expansion and/or quoting rules make it easily to accidentally cause shell injection when using custom commands with starship in bash. This issue only affects users with custom commands, so the scope is limited, and without knowledge of others' commands, it could be hard to successfully target someone. Version 1.20.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a prompt injection flaw in the Starship cross-shell prompt, which allows an attacker to manipulate shell commands in an unintended way. An attacker can exploit this by crafting a custom command that tricks Starship into executing malicious shell commands, potentially allowing them to gain unauthorized access or execute arbitrary code. If successfully exploited, the vulnerability can allow an attacker to steal sensitive information, install malware, or take control of the affected system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-4099</cve_id>
    <title>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output in GitLab</title>
    <vendor>GitLab</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>LOW</severity>
    <score>3.1</score>
    <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 17.2.8, from 17.3 prior to 17.3.4, and from 17.4 prior to 17.4.1. An AI feature was found to read unsanitized content in a way that could have allowed an attacker to hide prompt injection.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2024-4099 vulnerability:

CVE-2024-4099 is a Prompt Injection vulnerability, which occurs when an application reads unsanitized input and uses it to execute commands, allowing an attacker to inject malicious prompts.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by inserting crafted text into a prompt, which is then read by the AI feature without proper validation. This allows the attacker to manipulate the system and potentially gain unauthorized access.

If left unaddressed, this vulnerability can cause damage by allowing an attacker to gain control over the system, potentially leading to data breaches, unauthorized changes, and other malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-34359</cve_id>
    <title>llama-cpp-python vulnerable to Remote Code Execution by Server-Side Template Injection in Model Metadata</title>
    <vendor>abetlen</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.7</score>
    <description>llama-cpp-python is the Python bindings for llama.cpp. `llama-cpp-python` depends on class `Llama` in `llama.py` to load `.gguf` llama.cpp or Latency Machine Learning Models. The `__init__` constructor built in the `Llama` takes several parameters to configure the loading and running of the model. Other than `NUMA, LoRa settings`, `loading tokenizers,` and `hardware settings`, `__init__` also loads the `chat template` from targeted `.gguf` 's Metadata and furtherly parses it to `llama_chat_format.Jinja2ChatFormatter.to_chat_handler()` to construct the `self.chat_handler` for this model. Nevertheless, `Jinja2ChatFormatter` parse the `chat template` within the Metadate with sandbox-less `jinja2.Environment`, which is furthermore rendered in `__call__` to construct the `prompt` of interaction. This allows `jinja2` Server Side Template Injection which leads to remote code execution by a carefully constructed payload.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simplified explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a &quot;Prompt Injection&quot; flaw in the &quot;llama-cpp-python&quot; library, which allows attackers to inject malicious code into the system. Attackers can do this by crafting a specially designed payload in the chat template metadata, which is then rendered without security restrictions, allowing them to execute arbitrary code. This vulnerability allows attackers to gain remote control of the system, potentially leading to data theft, modification of sensitive data, or other types of cyber attacks.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-3303</cve_id>
    <title>Improper Neutralization of Input Used for LLM Prompting in GitLab</title>
    <vendor>GitLab</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.4</score>
    <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 17.6.5, starting from 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and starting from 17.8 prior to 17.8.2, which allows an attacker to exfiltrate contents of a private issue using prompt injection.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a type of prompt injection flaw in GitLab, which allows an attacker to trick the system into revealing sensitive information. The attacker exploits this by inserting malicious information in a field that expects user input, causing the system to reveal private issue contents unintentionally. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing attackers to steal sensitive data, potentially leading to data breaches, intellectual property theft, and reputational harm to organizations relying on GitLab.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-3098</cve_id>
    <title>Prompt Injection leading to Arbitrary Code Execution in run-llama/llama_index</title>
    <vendor>run-llama</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.8</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in the `exec_utils` class of the `llama_index` package, specifically within the `safe_eval` function, allowing for prompt injection leading to arbitrary code execution. This issue arises due to insufficient validation of input, which can be exploited to bypass method restrictions and execute unauthorized code. The vulnerability is a bypass of the previously addressed CVE-2023-39662, demonstrated through a proof of concept that creates a file on the system by exploiting the flaw.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2024-3098 vulnerability is a prompt injection attack that allows attackers to inject malicious code into a system through insufficient input validation in the `safe_eval` function of the `llama_index` package.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending specially crafted input to the system, which the `safe_eval` function mistakenly interprets as legitimate, allowing the attacker to bypass security restrictions and execute their own code.

This vulnerability can allow an attacker to execute unauthorized code, potentially resulting in system damage, data theft, or even complete system takeover, by creating or modifying system files and directories, as demonstrated in the proof of concept.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-25639</cve_id>
    <title>Prompt Injection triggered XSS vulnerability in Khoj Obsidian, Desktop and Web clients</title>
    <vendor>khoj-ai</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.9</score>
    <description>Khoj is an application that creates personal AI agents. The Khoj Obsidian, Desktop and Web clients inadequately sanitize the AI model's response and user inputs. This can trigger Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Prompt Injection from untrusted documents either indexed by the user on Khoj or read by Khoj from the internet when the user invokes the /online command. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.0.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2024-25639 occurs when the Khoj application fails to properly sanitize user inputs and AI model responses, allowing malicious code to be injected into the system. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by submitting a specially crafted prompt or input that tricks the Khoj application into executing malicious code, typically via the /online command. The damage that can be caused by this vulnerability includes allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information, inject malware, or take control of the user's account, potentially leading to financial loss or compromise of personal data.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-12911</cve_id>
    <title>SQL Injection in run-llama/llama_index</title>
    <vendor>run-llama</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.1</score>
    <description>A vulnerability in the `default_jsonalyzer` function of the `JSONalyzeQueryEngine` in the run-llama/llama_index repository allows for SQL injection via prompt injection. This can lead to arbitrary file creation and Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks. The vulnerability affects the latest version and is fixed in version 0.5.1.</description>
    <ai_explanation>This vulnerability is a type of Prompt Injection, where a malicious input is sent to the system, which then processes it as if it were a legitimate request. An attacker exploits this by crafting a malicious prompt that is used to inject SQL code, allowing them to potentially create arbitrary files or shut down the system. This can cause significant damage by enabling attackers to disrupt normal system operations or create unwanted data, leading to potential losses in sensitive information or even financial losses.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-10954</cve_id>
    <title>Prompt Injection Leading to RCE in binary-husky/gpt_academic Plugin `manim`</title>
    <vendor>binary-husky</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>In the `manim` plugin of binary-husky/gpt_academic, versions prior to the fix, a vulnerability exists due to improper handling of user-provided prompts. The root cause is the execution of untrusted code generated by the LLM without a proper sandbox. This allows an attacker to perform remote code execution (RCE) on the app backend server by injecting malicious code through the prompt.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in the `manim` plugin, known as CVE-2024-10954, is a type of Prompt Injection that allows an attacker to inject malicious code. The attacker exploits this by providing a specially crafted prompt that executes unauthorized code on the app backend server, which can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE). This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including the unauthorized takeover of the server, data theft, or the deployment of malware, potentially resulting in a complete system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2024-10950</cve_id>
    <title>Code Injection in binary-husky/gpt_academic</title>
    <vendor>binary-husky</vendor>
    <attack_type>Prompt Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>In binary-husky/gpt_academic version &lt;= 3.83, the plugin `CodeInterpreter` is vulnerable to code injection caused by prompt injection. The root cause is the execution of user-provided prompts that generate untrusted code without a sandbox, allowing the execution of parts of the LLM-generated code. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to achieve remote code execution (RCE) on the application backend server, potentially gaining full control of the server.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2024-10950 is a code injection issue that occurs when a plugin called CodeInterpreter executes user-provided prompts from a large language model (LLM) without proper security checks. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious prompts to the CodeInterpreter plugin, which would then unknowingly execute malicious code that allows the attacker to gain control of the server. This can cause significant damage by allowing the attacker to remotely execute arbitrary commands on the server's backend, potentially leading to a complete takeover of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7822</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Courier Management System print_pdets.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Courier Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /print_pdets.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are 3 simple sentences explaining the vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7822, is a SQL injection flaw in a specific function within the Courier Management System software, allowing attackers to manipulate database queries. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious inputs, such as fake IDs, to the software's /print_pdets.php file, which can be done remotely, and publicly available exploit tools can be used to do this. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can allow an attacker to access sensitive data, alter data, or even take control of the system, causing significant security breaches and potential data loss.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7783</cve_id>
    <title>CodeCanyon Perfex CRM Admin Kanban Endpoint AbstractKanban.php applySortQuery sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeCanyon</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in CodeCanyon Perfex CRM up to 3.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function AbstractKanban::applySortQuery of the file application/services/AbstractKanban.php of the component Admin Kanban Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument this causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the CodeCanyon Perfex CRM system, specifically in the Admin Kanban Endpoint, which can be exploited by manipulating the argument passed to the &quot;applySortQuery&quot; function in the &quot;AbstractKanban.php&quot; file.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the system, which can be done remotely, allowing them to access or modify sensitive data within the database. This exploitation can lead to unauthorized modifications, data breaches, or even takeover of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7746</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System edit-admin.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product_expiry/edit-admin.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7746 vulnerability is a SQL injection attack in the SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the ID argument in the /product_expiry/edit-admin.php file, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code. This can cause damage by allowing the attacker to access, modify, or delete sensitive data in the system, which could lead to the theft of personal or financial information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7745</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom facultydetails sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /OnlineClassroom/facultydetails. This manipulation of the argument deleteid causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7745 is a SQL injection flaw in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate data within the application's database. The attacker exploits it by sending a malicious request to the /OnlineClassroom/facultydetails page with a manipulated &quot;deleteid&quot; argument, which executes unintended SQL commands. This vulnerability can cause damage by allowing attackers to steal sensitive data, disrupt the application's functionality, and even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7744</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom addnewstudent sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /OnlineClassroom/addnewstudent. The manipulation of the argument fname results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>A vulnerability in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0 allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;fname&quot; field in the &quot;/OnlineClassroom/addnewstudent&quot; function, potentially sending malicious code to the system. This can cause significant damage by allowing the attacker to access sensitive data, modify database records, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7743</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom studentdetails sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /OnlineClassroom/studentdetails. The manipulation of the argument deleteid leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0 is a SQL injection issue, which allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the system. The attacker can exploit this by manipulating the 'deleteid' argument in the '/OnlineClassroom/studentdetails' file, allowing them to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, allowing the hacker to view, modify, or delete sensitive information, potentially putting the entire system at risk.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7742</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom facultylogin sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /OnlineClassroom/facultylogin. Executing a manipulation of the argument fid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is an SQL Injection flaw in the faculty login feature of the CodeAstro Online Classroom software, allowing an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker exploits this by manipulating the 'fid' argument in the /OnlineClassroom/facultylogin file, which allows them to execute their own malicious SQL commands. This can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive data and potentially allow an attacker to take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7741</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom studentlogin sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /OnlineClassroom/studentlogin. Performing a manipulation of the argument sid results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2026-7741, is a SQL injection flaw in the CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0, which allows an attacker to inject malicious code into the system. An attacker can exploit this by inserting malicious data into the &quot;sid&quot; argument of the /OnlineClassroom/studentlogin file, allowing them to access unauthorized data or even take control of the system remotely. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data theft, unauthorized changes to the system, and the potential to spread malware to other parts of the network.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7731</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects BloodBank Managing System get_state.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects BloodBank Managing System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file get_state.php. The manipulation of the argument G_STATE_ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7731 vulnerability is a Sql Injection flaw in the BloodBank Managing System 1.0's &quot;get_state.php&quot; file, where an attacker can manipulate a user-inputted variable.

An attacker exploits the vulnerability by inserting malicious SQL code into the input field of the system, often the &quot;G_STATE_ID&quot; variable, which can trick the system into giving away sensitive information or modifying vital data.

If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can cause damage such as unauthorized data access, system crashes, or even full data breaches, giving an attacker critical control over the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7727</cve_id>
    <title>Shandong Hoteam Software PDM Product Data Management System DataService GetQueryMachineGridOnePageData sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Shandong Hoteam Software</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in Shandong Hoteam Software PDM Product Data Management System up to 8.3.9. This affects the function GetQueryMachineGridOnePageData of the file /Base/BaseService.asmx/DataService. This manipulation of the argument SortOrder causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.3.10 is able to mitigate this issue. You should upgrade the affected component.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7727 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the Shandong Hoteam Software PDM Product Data Management System, which allows an attacker to manipulate the SortOrder argument. An attacker can remotely exploit this by injecting malicious SQL code, potentially giving them unauthorized access to sensitive data. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data theft, modification, or even complete system takeover if left unpatched.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7716</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Gym Management System In PHP/Windows NT index.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Gym Management System In PHP and Windows NT 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument day results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>A vulnerability known as CVE-2026-7716 allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the Gym Management System.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating input data, specifically the &quot;day&quot; argument, to inject malicious SQL code through the internet, which can then be executed by the system without the user's knowledge.

This vulnerability could potentially allow an attacker to steal sensitive data, modify critical information, or even completely take control of the affected system, compromising the security and integrity of the Gym Management System and potentially causing significant damage.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7699</cve_id>
    <title>Dromara MaxKey StrUtils.java StrUtils.checkSqlInjection sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Dromara</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in Dromara MaxKey up to 3.5.13. Affected by this issue is the function StrUtils.checkSqlInjection of the file StrUtils.java. Performing a manipulation of the argument filtersfields results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-7699 vulnerability:

A SQL injection vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the MaxKey system, potentially granting them unauthorized access to sensitive data. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the &quot;filtersfields&quot; argument in the StrUtils.checkSqlInjection function, allowing them to inject malicious SQL commands remotely. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can lead to data theft, unauthorized modifications, or even complete system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7697</cve_id>
    <title>AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System cardhand_submit.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>AMTT</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manager/card/cardhand_submit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7697 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System 1.0, specifically in a file called cardhand_submit.php.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a maliciously crafted ID argument to the affected file, which allows them to inject and execute unintended SQL commands, compromising the system's security.

If successfully exploited, this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive data, modification of system settings, or even complete system takeover, potentially resulting in financial loss, data theft, or disruption of critical services.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7695</cve_id>
    <title>Acrel Electrical EEMS Enterprise Power Operation and Maintenance Cloud Platform elecMaxMinAvgValue sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Acrel Electrical</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in Acrel Electrical EEMS Enterprise Power Operation and Maintenance Cloud Platform 1.3.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /SubstationWEBV2/main/elecMaxMinAvgValue. The manipulation of the argument fCircuitids leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's the simplified explanation of the CVE-2026-7695 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL Injection bug that allows an attacker to manipulate a function within the Acrel Electrical EEMS Enterprise Power Operation and Maintenance Cloud Platform, potentially leading to sensitive data exposure.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by inputting malicious SQL code into the &quot;fCircuitids&quot; argument, which can be done remotely, giving the attacker control over the compromised system.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, modification of database records, and potentially even complete system takeover, all of which can compromise the security and integrity of the affected platform.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7694</cve_id>
    <title>Acrel Electrical ECEMS Enterprise Microgrid Energy Efficiency Management System elecMaxMinAvgValue sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Acrel Electrical</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in Acrel Electrical ECEMS Enterprise Microgrid Energy Efficiency Management System 1.3.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /SubstationWEBV2/main/elecMaxMinAvgValue. Executing a manipulation of the argument fCircuitids can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7694 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection flaw in a software system called Acrel Electrical ECEMS, which can be exploited by an attacker to access sensitive information.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a specific argument called &quot;fCircuitids&quot; in a file called &quot;elecMaxMinAvgValue&quot;, allowing them to inject malicious SQL commands that can extract or modify sensitive data.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, potentially allowing an attacker to gain unauthorized access to critical system information, disrupt the normal operation of the energy management system, and even lead to financial or reputational losses for the affected organizations.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7688</cve_id>
    <title>Dolibarr ERP CRM Shipments API Endpoint expedition.class.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Dolibarr</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>5.0</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in Dolibarr ERP CRM up to 23.0.2. This affects the function _checkValForAPI of the file htdocs/expedition/class/expedition.class.php of the component Shipments API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument fields leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is an SQL injection flaw in Dolibarr ERP CRM's Shipments API Endpoint, which can be exploited by manipulating the &quot;fields&quot; argument.

An attacker could exploit this flaw by submitting specially crafted input to the &quot;fields&quot; argument, effectively allowing them to execute malicious SQL code and potentially extract sensitive data or gain unauthorized access.

This exploitation can lead to a range of damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, disruption of business operations, or even full control of the system by the attacker.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7678</cve_id>
    <title>YunaiV yudao-cloud GoViewDataServiceImpl.java getDataBySQL sql injection</title>
    <vendor>YunaiV</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in YunaiV yudao-cloud up to 2026.01. This affects the function getDataBySQL of the file yudao-module-report-biz/src/main/java/io/github/ruoyi/report/service/impl/GoViewDataServiceImpl.java. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7678 is a SQL injection flaw in YunaiV's yudao-cloud system, which allows attackers to inject malicious SQL code into the system. An attacker exploits this by sending specially crafted inputs to the getDataBySQL function, allowing them to manipulate the system's database and access sensitive information. This can cause significant damage, including data theft, system compromise, and potentially even unauthorized access to sensitive user data.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7672</cve_id>
    <title>youlaitech youlai-boot Users Endpoint UserController.java getUserList sql injection</title>
    <vendor>youlaitech</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in youlaitech youlai-boot up to 2.21.1. This affects the function getUserList of the file src/main/java/com/youlai/boot/system/controller/UserController.java of the component Users Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument order leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7672 vulnerability is a SQL injection issue that affects the getUserList function in the UserController.java file of the Youlai Boot component. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the order of arguments in a request, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code that can access or modify sensitive data. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including the unauthorized access or theft of sensitive user information and potentially allow the attacker to take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7670</cve_id>
    <title>Jinher OA UserSel.aspx sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Jinher</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in Jinher OA 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /C6/JHSoft.Web.PlanSummarize/UserSel.aspx. This manipulation of the argument DeptIDList causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7670, is a SQL injection flaw that allows attackers to manipulate the input data in the &quot;/C6/JHSoft.Web.PlanSummarize/UserSel.aspx&quot; file, potentially exposing sensitive database information. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by crafting a malicious input, known as DeptIDList, which injects malicious SQL code into the database, enabling them to extract or modify critical data. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data theft, unauthorized changes, and potentially even allow the attacker to take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7649</cve_id>
    <title>ARMember &lt;= 4.0.60 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via 'orderby' Parameter</title>
    <vendor>reputeinfosystems</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.5</score>
    <description>The ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.60 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7649 allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into a WordPress plugin called ARMember, which can retrieve sensitive information from the database.

Attackers exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the 'orderby' parameter to insert additional SQL queries that extract sensitive data, such as passwords or user IDs. This can allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information, leading to potential data breaches and identity theft.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7632</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Online Hospital Management System viewappointment.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /viewappointment.php. This manipulation of the argument delid causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>A CVE-2026-7632 vulnerability is a SQL Injection weakness in the Online Hospital Management System 1.0, specifically in the /viewappointment.php file. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the 'delid' argument to inject malicious SQL code, which can be done remotely and has been publicly disclosed. This exploit can cause damage by allowing an attacker to access or modify sensitive database information, potentially leading to data theft, system disruption, or unauthorized changes to the hospital management system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7612</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Courier Management System edit_user.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit_user.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7612 vulnerability is a type of SQL Injection, which means an attacker can inject malicious code into a database to extract or manipulate sensitive data. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;ID&quot; argument in the &quot;/edit_user.php&quot; file, which can lead to unauthorized access to the database. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data theft, modification, or deletion, allowing the attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7592</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Courier Management System edit_staff.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /edit_staff.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-7592 vulnerability:

The CVE-2026-7592 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the Courier Management System 1.0, specifically in the /edit_staff.php file, which lets attackers manipulate the system's database. An attacker exploits this by sending a specially crafted request with manipulated data for the ID argument, allowing them to access and potentially alter sensitive database information. If successful, this attack could allow an attacker to extract or modify confidential data, disrupt system operations, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7591</cve_id>
    <title>TimBroddin astro-mcp-server MCP Tool Query Construction index.ts sql injection</title>
    <vendor>TimBroddin</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in TimBroddin astro-mcp-server up to 1.1.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file src/index.ts of the component MCP Tool Query Construction. Performing a manipulation of the argument request.params.arguments results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7591, is a SQL Injection vulnerability that allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the system. An attacker exploits it by manipulating a request parameter to inject SQL code, which can be done remotely, allowing the attacker to access sensitive data. This vulnerability can cause damage by potentially allowing attackers to steal or modify sensitive data, potentially leading to data breaches or unauthorized changes to the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7555</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Electronic Judging System login.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Electronic Judging System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /intrams/login.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7555 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection attack that occurs when an attacker manipulates user input, specifically the &quot;Username&quot; field, in the /intrams/login.php file of the itsourcecode Electronic Judging System 1.0. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the Username field, allowing them to access, modify, or delete sensitive data within the database. This attack can lead to unauthorized access to user information, grades, or other sensitive data, potentially compromising the integrity and security of the Electronic Judging System.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7553</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Gym Management System edit_exercises.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_exercises.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_exercise results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;Gym Management System 1.0&quot;, found in the file &quot;/admin/edit_exercises.php&quot;.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating user input to inject malicious SQL code, allowing them to access or manipulate sensitive data remotely.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data, potentially leading to data theft, system compromise, or other malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7550</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php save_customer sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_customer. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are three simple sentences explaining the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a &quot;sql injection&quot; in a software called SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System that allows an attacker to insert malicious code into the system. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;ID&quot; argument in the &quot;/ajax.php?action=save_customer&quot; file to trick the system into running the attacker's malicious commands, which can be done remotely over the internet. If successful, the attacker can gain unauthorized access to sensitive data and potentially delete or alter critical information, causing significant damage to the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7549</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php delete_customer sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_customer. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7549 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection attack that affects a web application called SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System. An attacker can exploit it by manipulating the ID argument in the /ajax.php?action=delete_customer URL to execute malicious SQL commands, which allows the attacker to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing the attacker to steal sensitive customer information, delete or manipulate database records, and potentially take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7545</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Advanced School Management System checkEmail Endpoint commonController.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Advanced School Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file commonController.php of the component checkEmail Endpoint. This manipulation causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7545 is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Advanced School Management System 1.0, which allows an attacker to manipulate database commands through user input. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by submitting malicious input that tricks the system into executing unauthorized database queries, thereby accessing or modifying sensitive data. The damage this vulnerability can cause includes unauthorized access to sensitive information, data manipulation, and even complete system takeover, giving the attacker control over the affected system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7506</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Hotel Management System check sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Hotel Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /index.php/reservation/check. Such manipulation of the argument room_type leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Hotel Management System 1.0, which allows attackers to inject malicious SQL code into the system's database. The attacker exploits this by manipulating the &quot;room_type&quot; argument in the &quot;/index.php/reservation/check&quot; file, allowing them to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including data breaches, unauthorized access, or even complete system takeover, allowing the attacker to steal sensitive information or disrupt the system's operation.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7489</cve_id>
    <title>Sunnet｜CTMS - SQL Injection</title>
    <vendor>Sunnet</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>8.8</score>
    <description>CTMS developed by Sunnet has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7489 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection that affects a specific database system used by Sunnet's CTMS software. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious SQL commands to the system through the software, allowing them to access sensitive information. This vulnerability allows an attacker to read, modify, or even delete critical data, potentially leading to devastating consequences for the affected organization.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7447</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software update_customer.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/update_customer.php. This manipulation of the argument type/length/business parameter validity causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>A vulnerability in the SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. Attacker can do this by sending specially crafted input to the /admin/update_customer.php page, which can then be used to manipulate the database. This vulnerability can cause damage by allowing an attacker to access, modify or delete sensitive customer information, potentially causing financial losses or identity theft.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7435</cve_id>
    <title>SSCMS v7.4.0 SQL Injection via stl:sqlContent queryString</title>
    <vendor>siteserver</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.2</score>
    <description>SSCMS v7.4.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the stl:sqlContent tag where the queryString attribute is passed directly to database execution without parameterization or sanitization. Attackers can craft encrypted payloads submitted to the /api/stl/actions/dynamic endpoint to execute arbitrary SQL statements, leading to unauthorized database access, data disclosure, authentication bypass, data modification, or complete database compromise.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability in 3 sentences:

CVE-2026-7435 is a SQL injection vulnerability in a website's database system, allowing attackers to inject malicious code to access the database. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a malicious payload to the website's /api/stl/actions/dynamic endpoint, which is then executed by the database as if it were a legitimate query. This can cause the attacker to access unauthorized data, steal sensitive information, or even take control of the entire database system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7410</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php add_to_cart sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=add_to_cart. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7410 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw that occurs in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0, specifically in the /admin/ajax.php?action=add_to_cart file. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;pid&quot; argument in a way that allows them to inject malicious SQL code, which can be initiated remotely. If successful, an attacker can cause damage by accessing and manipulating sensitive data, potentially leading to unauthorized changes or theft of sensitive customer information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7409</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php save_user sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This affects the function save_user of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_user. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-7409 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a type of SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0, which allows an attacker to manipulate the system's database queries.

The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending specially crafted input to the system's 'save_user' function in the 'ajax.php' file, which enables them to inject malicious SQL code and gain unauthorized access to the database.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can allow an attacker to extract sensitive data, tamper with user accounts, or even take control of the entire system, potentially resulting in the loss of sensitive customer information and financial data.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7408</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php save_menu sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function save_menu of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_menu. Performing a manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7408, is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System's save_menu function, located in the /admin/ajax.php?action=save_menu file.

An attacker can remotely exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious SQL code through the system, potentially tricking the system into performing unauthorized actions or revealing sensitive data.

If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can cause damage such as allowing attackers to access sensitive user data, modify or delete critical system information, or even execute malicious SQL queries to disrupt the system's functionality.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7407</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System Setting ajax.php save_settings sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_settings of the file /pizzafy/admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings of the component Setting Handler. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the vulnerability:

CVE-2026-7407 is a SQL injection vulnerability in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0, which allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the system's database. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted input to the system's /pizzafy/admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings page, allowing them to access or modify sensitive data in the database. This vulnerability can cause damage by allowing an attacker to steal sensitive information, delete or modify data, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7394</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System GET Parameter view_order.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/view_order.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7394 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System's /admin/view_order.php file, allowing attackers to manipulate the &quot;ID&quot; parameter and execute malicious SQL code.

The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted GET request to the /admin/view_order.php file, which includes malicious SQL code within the &quot;ID&quot; parameter, allowing the attacker to extract sensitive data or disrupt the application.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive customer information, disruption of the ecommerce system, and potentially even complete control of the application, allowing the attacker to steal sensitive data, delete orders, or make unauthorized changes to the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7392</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php delete_supplier sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This impacts the function delete_supplier of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_supplier. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-7392 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection in the Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, specifically in the delete_supplier function, allowing an attacker to manipulate database queries on the system. An attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted request, possibly from a remote location, to make the system execute malicious SQL commands unintentionally. If exploited successfully, this can cause unauthorized access to sensitive data or disrupt the entire system, potentially resulting in loss of sensitive information, financial data, or complete system downtime.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7391</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php save_supplier sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects the function save_supplier of the file /ajax.php?action=save_supplier. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7391 is a SQL Injection vulnerability in an online Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the 'ID' parameter in the '/ajax.php?action=save_supplier' function with malicious SQL code to access and modify sensitive data, often through a website form. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing attackers to extract and delete data, inject malicious code, and gain unauthorized access to sensitive information, ultimately compromising the system's security and integrity.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7389</cve_id>
    <title>EyouCMS common.php GetSortData sql injection</title>
    <vendor>n/a</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in EyouCMS up to 1.7.9. The affected element is the function GetSortData of the file application/common.php. The manipulation of the argument sort_asc leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7389 is a SQL injection bug in the EyouCMS up to version 1.7.9. Attackers can exploit it by manipulating the &quot;sort_asc&quot; argument in a URL or input field, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code into the system and potentially gain access to sensitive data or take control of the application. This can cause significant damage, such as data breaches, system crashes, and even unauthorized changes to the application's database.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7293</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php delete_category sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Affected is the function delete_category of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7293 is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0, specifically in the &quot;delete_category&quot; function. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted &quot;ID&quot; to the vulnerable &quot;ajax.php&quot; page, allowing them to execute malicious SQL commands on the database. This can cause significant damage, including allowing the attacker to access, modify or delete sensitive data, potentially leading to the complete compromise of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7290</cve_id>
    <title>JeecgBoot loadDict Endpoint SqlInjectionUtil.java SqlInjectionUtil sql injection</title>
    <vendor>n/a</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.1. Impacted is the function SqlInjectionUtil of the file jeecg-boot/jeecg-boot-base-core/src/main/java/org/jeecg/common/util/SqlInjectionUtil.java of the component loadDict Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument keyword causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: a9c8e8eb1185751c4c3c68d2a53f3dadee9edc6b. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-7290 vulnerability in 3 simple sentences:

The vulnerability is a SQL Injection issue in the JeecgBoot software, which allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code through the loadDict endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the keyword argument in the endpoint, allowing them to access or modify sensitive data remotely. This attack can cause significant damage, including data theft, tampering, or even complete system takeover, especially if the JeecgBoot software is used in production environments.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7283</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php save_expired sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This impacts the function save_expired of the file /ajax.php?action=save_expired. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7283 is a SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System, which allows attackers to manipulate database queries. The attacker exploits it by sending a maliciously crafted &quot;ID&quot; value to the /ajax.php?action=save_expired page, which is then executed as a SQL query, giving the attacker control over the database. This can cause damage by allowing the attacker to steal sensitive information, delete critical data, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7282</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php delete_expired sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects the function delete_expired of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_expired. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7282 is a SQL injection problem in the Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System, which allows attackers to manipulate database queries. An attacker exploits it by injecting malicious SQL code into the &quot;ID&quot; field, allowing unauthorized access or manipulation of sensitive data. This can cause significant damage, such as stealing or modifying important information, deleting data, or even taking control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7268</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php save_category sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This impacts the function save_category of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_category. Such manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerabilityCVE-2026-7268 is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;save_category&quot; function of the Pizzafy Ecommerce System's /admin/ajax.php file, allowing an attacker to manipulate database queries. An attacker can exploit this flaw by sending malicious data, specifically modifying the &quot;Name&quot; argument, to execute unauthorized SQL code, potentially allowing access to sensitive data or system manipulation. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive information, data tampering, or even a full system takeover.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7267</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System view_prod.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view_prod.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>CVE-2026-7267 is a vulnerability that allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the system, potentially disrupting the entire database. An attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted ID to the vulnerable webpage, usually /view_prod.php, which will cause the system to execute the malicious SQL code, allowing the attacker to access sensitive information. This can cause significant damage, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive customer data, manipulate orders or products, or even take full control of the ecommerce system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7266</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php save_order sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. The impacted element is the function save_order of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_order. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7266 vulnerability is an SQL Injection issue in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System's save_order function, allowing an attacker to manipulate SQL code to extract sensitive data.

An attacker would exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious input to the save_order function in /admin/ajax.php?action=save_order, allowing them to execute unauthorized SQL commands and potentially access sensitive user information.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, allowing an attacker to extract sensitive user data, gain unauthorized access to the system, and even take control of the entire ecommerce system, potentially compromising financial and customer information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7265</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System index.php category sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. The affected element is the function Category of the file pizza/index.php?page=category. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7265 vulnerability is a type of Sql Injection, specifically in the function Category of the file pizza/index.php?page=category. An attacker can exploit this by sending a malicious input, such as a specially crafted query in the ID field, to manipulate the database and gain unauthorized access. This can cause damage by allowing an attacker to modify or delete sensitive data, or even completely take control of the system, potentially leading to data breaches and financial loss.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7264</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php get_cart_items sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Impacted is the function get_cart_items of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=get_cart_items. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are 3 simple sentences explaining the vulnerability:

The vulnerability CVE-2026-7264 is a SQL Injection bug in the &quot;Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0&quot; which allows an attacker to manipulate the system. An attacker can exploit this issue remotely by entering special characters into the &quot;ID&quot; field, allowing them to access and modify sensitive data, possibly including financial information. This SQL Injection attack can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to user data, disruption of the system, and potential financial losses through theft or manipulation of orders.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7229</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Coaching Management System POST reply.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Coaching Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /cims/modules/admin/reply.php of the component POST Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument complaintreply results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simplified explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in a function within the Coaching Management System 1.0, which allows an attacker to manipulate database queries. An attacker exploits this by sending a specially crafted message to the system's complaint reply feature, allowing them to execute arbitrary SQL commands remotely. This could allow an attacker to access sensitive data, manipulate the database, or even gain control over the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7228</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php get_cart_count sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. The affected element is the function get_cart_count of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=get_cart_count. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;get_cart_count&quot; function of the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System, which allows an attacker to manipulate user input. An attacker can exploit this by sending malicious input to the website, allowing them to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can cause data breaches, unauthorized changes to the system, and even financial losses for the affected e-commerce business.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7227</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php login sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. Impacted is the function Login of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument e-mail results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7227 vulnerability is a SQL injection security flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System, specifically affecting its login feature.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious SQL code into the system through the login email field, allowing them to extract or modify sensitive data.

If exploited successfully, the attacker can cause significant damage, such as stealing customer personal data, gaining unauthorized access to the admin panel, or even completely taking control of the e-commerce system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7226</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php login2 sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This issue affects the function login2 of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login2. The manipulation of the argument e-mail leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-7226 vulnerability in simple terms:

This is a sql injection vulnerability, which means an attacker can trick the system into executing malicious database commands by manipulating user input, specifically email addresses in this case. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL commands through the login feature of the Pizzafy Ecommerce System, potentially allowing them to access sensitive data or manipulate the system. If exploited, this vulnerability can cause the system to become unstable or allow attackers to steal customer data, passwords, or other sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7225</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php delete_menu sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function delete_menu of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_menu. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0, specifically in the &quot;delete_menu&quot; function. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the ID argument with malicious SQL code, allowing them to potentially access, modify, or delete sensitive data. This attack can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to disrupt or steal sensitive information from the ecommerce system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7224</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System ajax.php delete_cart sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0. This affects the function delete_cart of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_cart. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7224 is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pizzafy Ecommerce System 1.0 that allows an attacker to manipulate the system's database. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted ID to the &quot;delete_cart&quot; function in the /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_cart file, which allows them to execute malicious SQL code remotely. This exploit can cause damage by allowing an attacker to modify or delete sensitive data in the database, potentially leading to the theft or alteration of customer and financial information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7206</cve_id>
    <title>dubydu sqlite-mcp extract_to_json sql injection</title>
    <vendor>dubydu</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in dubydu sqlite-mcp up to 0.1.0. The affected element is the function extract_to_json of the file src/entry.py. Performing a manipulation of the argument output_filename results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is named a5580cb992f4f6c308c9ffe6442b2e76709db548. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;extract_to_json&quot; function in a Python file called &quot;entry.py&quot;. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the &quot;output_filename&quot; argument, allowing them to execute malicious SQL commands on the database. If successful, this could allow an attacker to access sensitive information, modify database content, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7199</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_product. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7199 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, specifically in the &quot;/ajax.php?action=delete_product&quot; functionality. An attacker can exploit this by sending malicious input, such as altering the &quot;ID&quot; argument, which can trick the system into executing unintended SQL commands remotely. This exploitation can result in unauthorized data access, modification, or even complete system takeover, potentially leading to sensitive customer or financial information being compromised.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7196</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom guestdetails sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /guestdetails. Such manipulation of the argument deleteid leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>CVE-2026-7196 is a SQL Injection vulnerability, which means that an attacker can insert malicious SQL code into a website to try to steal, modify, or delete sensitive data.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request to the /guestdetails page, including malicious code in the deleteid parameter, which allows them to execute arbitrary SQL commands on the database.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to read or modify sensitive data, such as user passwords, grades, and other personal information, potentially compromising the entire online classroom system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7194</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_product. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, which allows an attacker to manipulate the system's database.

An attacker exploits this by injecting malicious SQL code into the '/ajax.php?action=save_product' part of the system's URL, potentially allowing them to access, modify, or delete sensitive data.

This can cause damage by allowing an attacker to gain unauthorized access to confidential information, such as customer records, product prices, or financial data, which can compromise the security and integrity of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7148</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Classroom addnewfaculty sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Online Classroom 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /addnewfaculty. Executing a manipulation of the argument fname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7148 vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code into the CodeAstro Online Classroom's &quot;fname&quot; argument, potentially granting them unauthorized access to sensitive data or manipulating the application's database.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by remotely sending a manipulated &quot;fname&quot; argument to the /addnewfaculty file, hoping that the system does not properly sanitize and sanitize the input. If successful, the attacker can inject malicious SQL commands that can manipulate the database.

If the attacker successfully injects malicious SQL code, they can cause significant damage, such as stealing sensitive user data, deleting or modifying essential records, or even gaining full control over the affected system and its associated resources.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7143</cve_id>
    <title>1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA block_status.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA up to 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/block_status.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7143 vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw in the 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System. An attacker exploits this by inserting malicious SQL code into the 'q' argument in the /admin/block_status.php file, allowing them to access and modify sensitive data remotely. This can lead to damage such as data theft or even complete system takeover, giving the attacker control over the entire system and its sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7131</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Online Lot Reservation System loginuser.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Lot Reservation System up to 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /loginuser.php. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7131 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the login system of an online lot reservation system. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious SQL code into the email or password fields, which the system will then execute unknowingly, allowing the attacker to access sensitive data or manipulate the system. This can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to user data, disruption of the system, and potential theft of sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7130</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_category. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7130 vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate database queries.

An attacker exploits this by sending a malicious input to the /ajax.php?action=delete_category URL, which can trick the system into executing unauthorized SQL commands. 

This vulnerability can cause damage by allowing an attacker to access, modify, or delete sensitive data from the system's database, potentially leading to unauthorized access or disruption of the pharmacy's sales and inventory management.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7128</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=save_type. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7128 is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, specifically in the /ajax.php?action=save_type file. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the 'ID' argument in the URL, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code and potentially steal or modify sensitive data. This attack can damage the system by allowing unauthorized access to confidential information, enabling an attacker to steal or delete sensitive data, and even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7127</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_receiving. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7127, is a SQL injection vulnerability in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0 software that allows an attacker to manipulate the system's database. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the system when the user attempts to delete a receiving item, potentially taking control of the entire database. This can cause significant damage to the system and even the company's operations, allowing an attacker to access sensitive information, modify records, or even lock the system entirely.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7126</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=save_category. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, specifically in the /ajax.php?action=save_category file. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the ID argument in the /ajax.php?action=save_category URL, tricking the system into executing malicious SQL code. If successful, the attack can damage the system by allowing the attacker to access sensitive data, modify or delete records, and potentially gain control over the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7118</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Employee Management System cancel.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Employee Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file 370project/cancel.php. The manipulation of the argument id/token leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7118, is an SQL injection flaw that affects the Employee Management System 1.0, allowing attackers to manipulate the database.

Attackers can exploit this flaw by inputting malicious code, often in the form of a URL or user input, which tricks the system into running unauthorized database commands. 

This exploitation can allow attackers to access sensitive data, modify or delete records, or even gain full control of the system, causing significant damage to the company's data, reputation, and financial security.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7117</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Employee Management System approve.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Employee Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file 370project/approve.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument id/token can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7117 is a SQL injection flaw in the Employee Management System 1.0, which can be exploited by injecting malicious code into the database. An attacker can do this by manipulating a parameter called &quot;id/token&quot; in the approve.php file, allowing them to access sensitive information or control the database remotely. If left unpatched, this vulnerability can cause significant damage, potentially leading to theft of employee data, unauthorized access to sensitive information, or even complete database takeover.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7115</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Employee Management System delete.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file 370project/delete.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7115, is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;Employee Management System 1.0&quot; that allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker could exploit this by sending fake employee ID numbers to the &quot;delete.php&quot; file, which would execute the malicious SQL code behind the scenes, allowing the attacker to access or manipulate data. The attack could lead to unauthorized access or modification of sensitive employee information, potentially causing data breaches, financial loss, or damage to the organization's reputation.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7114</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Employee Management System edit.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file 370project/edit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7114 vulnerability is a type of SQL Injection attack in the Employee Management System 1.0, where an attacker can manipulate the input data to access or modify sensitive database information. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted input to the &quot;ID&quot; field in the &quot;370project/edit.php&quot; file, usually done remotely, which allows them to access unauthorized data. This attack can cause significant damage, potentially leading to stolen or tampered employee data, unauthorized account access, or even a complete takeover of the employee management system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7103</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Chat System MD5 Hash update_user.php weak hash</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>3.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Chat System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file update_user.php of the component MD5 Hash Handler. This manipulation of the argument Password causes use of weak hash. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7103 is a SQL injection flaw in a specific PHP file, allowing attackers to manipulate database queries. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the &quot;Password&quot; field, which can execute unauthorized database operations remotely. This can lead to sensitive data exposure and unauthorized access to user accounts, potentially compromising the entire system's security.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7088</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_receiving. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7088 is a SQL Injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, which allows attackers to manipulate the system's database through a vulnerable function in /ajax.php?action=save_receiving.

Attackers can exploit this weakness by sending a specifically crafted ID to the vulnerable function, which will execute malicious SQL commands that the system should not run, essentially allowing the attacker to access or modify sensitive data.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to user data, modification of vital system settings, or even complete takeover of the system, which could lead to theft of sensitive information, financial loss, or other malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7087</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_sales. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7087, is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0 that allows hackers to manipulate the system's database. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request that tricks the system into executing malicious SQL code, which can be done remotely by anyone. This can cause significant damage by allowing hackers to access, modify, or delete sensitive data, such as customer information, financial records, and sales history.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7083</cve_id>
    <title>likeadmin-likeshop likeadmin_php dataTable Admin API DataTableLists.php queryResult sql injection</title>
    <vendor>likeadmin-likeshop</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in likeadmin-likeshop likeadmin_php up to 1.9.6. Affected by this issue is the function queryResult of the file server\app\adminapi\lists\tools\DataTableLists.php of the component dataTable Admin API. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-7083 vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability, known as SQL Injection, allows an attacker to inject malicious code into a website's database by manipulating user input. An attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted request to the website, which can then execute unauthorized database queries, giving the attacker access to sensitive information. The damage caused by exploiting this vulnerability can include the theft of sensitive data, unauthorized account access, and potentially even the complete control of the website's database.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7077</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Courier Management System edit_parcel.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Courier Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /edit_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-7077 vulnerability in simple terms:

CVE-2026-7077 is a SQL injection vulnerability, which means an attacker can inject malicious code into the system's database to extract or modify sensitive information.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by entering a carefully crafted ID number into the /edit_parcel.php file, potentially gaining access to sensitive data or even taking control of the database.

If exploited successfully, an attacker can cause significant damage, such as stealing or deleting sensitive data, modifying the system's behavior, or even taking over the entire system, which can lead to financial loss, compromised user information, or a complete system failure.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7076</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Courier Management System edit_branch.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Courier Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /edit_branch.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7076 is a SQL injection flaw in the Courier Management System 1.0, specifically in the /edit_branch.php file, which can allow an attacker to manipulate the system's database.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending manipulated input (ID) to the vulnerable file, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code that can be executed by the system, giving them unauthorized access to the database.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to steal sensitive data, delete or alter critical information, and potentially even take control of the system, leading to a full-blown security breach.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7075</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Construction Management System locations.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Construction Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /locations.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument address results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-7075 is a SQL injection issue in the 'iSourceCode Construction Management System 1.0' that allows attackers to manipulate data. The attacker exploits this issue by injecting malicious SQL code into the system through the &quot;/locations.php&quot; file, usually done by manipulating the &quot;address&quot; field, thus allowing unauthorized access to sensitive data. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can cause significant damage, such as data theft, system instability, and potentially even full system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7074</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Construction Management System execute1.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Construction Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /execute1.php. Such manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection in the &quot;isourcecode Construction Management System 1.0&quot; which allows an attacker to manipulate the code. The attacker exploits it by sending malicious input to the affected file &quot;/execute1.php&quot; which can execute unauthorized database operations remotely. This can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, data tampering, and potentially even a complete takeover of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7073</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Construction Management System execute.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Construction Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /execute.php. This manipulation of the argument code causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7073 vulnerability is a weakness in the &quot;isourcecode Construction Management System 1.0&quot; that allows malicious SQL code to be injected and run. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending specially crafted code to the vulnerable &quot;/execute.php&quot; file, which can then be used to extract, modify, or delete sensitive data. This can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to access, alter, or steal sensitive information stored in the system's database.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7072</cve_id>
    <title>CodePanda Source canteen_management_system login.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodePanda Source</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in CodePanda Source canteen_management_system 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7072 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the &quot;canteen_management_system&quot; software, specifically in the &quot;/api/login.php&quot; file, where an attacker can inject malicious SQL code.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted username to the &quot;/api/login.php&quot; file, allowing them to manipulate the database and potentially retrieve sensitive information or gain unauthorized access.

This attack can cause severe damage, including unauthorized access to user accounts, data breaches, and modification or deletion of critical database records, allowing attackers to manipulate essential data within the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7070</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Inventory Management System Login sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Login. Executing a manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

CVE-2026-7070 is a SQL injection vulnerability in the Inventory Management System 1.0, specifically in the login component, which allows attackers to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the 'Username' field to inject malicious SQL code, which can be done remotely and doesn't require the attacker to be logged in. This vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing attackers to extract sensitive data, create new user accounts, or even take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7063</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Employee Management System Endpoint eprocess.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /370project/process/eprocess.php of the component Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument pwd results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the Employee Management System 1.0, specifically in the eprocess.php file, which allows attackers to manipulate data.

Attackers exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the &quot;pwd&quot; argument, effectively inserting malicious SQL code into the system, allowing them to access or manipulate sensitive data.

This SQL injection can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to employee or user data, as well as potential data breaches or manipulation, which can lead to identity theft or financial losses.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7028</cve_id>
    <title>CodeAstro Online Job Portal All Jobs delete-jobs.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>CodeAstro</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in CodeAstro Online Job Portal 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/jobs-admins/delete-jobs.php of the component All Jobs Page. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-7028, is an SQL injection flaw found in the CodeAstro Online Job Portal 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate the &quot;ID&quot; argument in a way that inserts malicious SQL code. An attacker exploits this by passing a specially crafted ID through the delete-jobs.php page, which can then run the attacker's malicious SQL code remotely. This can damage the database by deleting or modifying sensitive data, potentially allowing an attacker to take control of the system or steal sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7023</cve_id>
    <title>ByteDance coze-studio databaseTool database_impl.go ExecuteSQL sql injection</title>
    <vendor>ByteDance</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in ByteDance coze-studio up to 0.5.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ExecuteSQL of the file backend/domain/memory/database/service/database_impl.go of the component databaseTool. Performing a manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>A vulnerability called SQL Injection has been discovered in a software tool called coze-studio, commonly used by ByteDance. The attacker can exploit this weakness by injecting malicious SQL code, which is then executed by the software, allowing the attacker to access sensitive data they shouldn't have. This can lead to unauthorized access to important information, such as user data or financial records, potentially resulting in identity theft or fraud.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-7002</cve_id>
    <title>KLiK SocialMediaWebsite Private Message get_message_ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>KLiK</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in KLiK SocialMediaWebsite up to 1.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /includes/get_message_ajax.php of the component Private Message Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument c_id can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-7002 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection flaw that affects the Private Message Handler component in a website's code. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;c_id&quot; argument in a way that allows them to inject malicious SQL code remotely, potentially giving them unauthorized access to sensitive user data. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to data breaches and unauthorized access to sensitive information, allowing attackers to extract or modify sensitive data such as user passwords and messages.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6991</cve_id>
    <title>colinhacks Zod CUID Data Type regexes.ts sql injection</title>
    <vendor>colinhacks</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in colinhacks Zod up to 4.3.6. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file packages/zod/src/v4/core/regexes.ts of the component CUID Data Type Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-6991 vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL Injection issue in the Zod up to version 4.3.6, allowing an attacker to manipulate data in a way that can read and alter sensitive database information. An attacker can exploit this by sending malicious inputs to the vulnerable system, which then executes the attacker's SQL code, resulting in unauthorized access to data. This can cause significant damage, including data theft, modification, or even complete system compromise, leading to a loss of sensitive information and potential financial harm.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6982</cve_id>
    <title>star7th ShowDoc API Page Sort Endpoint PageController.class.PHP sql injection</title>
    <vendor>star7th</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in star7th ShowDoc up to 2.10.10/3.6.2/3.8.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file server/Application/Api/Controller/PageController.class.PHP of the component API Page Sort Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument pages can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 3.8.1 addresses this issue. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. According to the researcher, &quot;[t]he vendor explicitly stated they will not backport patches to the older affected versions.&quot;</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-6982 vulnerability is a SQL injection attack that affects the &quot;Page Sort Endpoint&quot; in the star7th ShowDoc component. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;pages&quot; argument, which can allow them to inject malicious SQL code and access unauthorized data. If successfully exploited, this vulnerability can cause data breaches, allowing attackers to steal sensitive information or disrupt the functionality of the affected system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6978</cve_id>
    <title>JiZhiCMS addcache.html htmlspecialchars_decode sql injection</title>
    <vendor>n/a</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>4.7</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in JiZhiCMS up to 2.5.6. The impacted element is the function htmlspecialchars_decode of the file /index.php/admins/Sys/addcache.html. The manipulation of the argument sqls results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection issue in JiZhiCMS version 2.5.6, which allows attackers to manipulate the data that the system uses to interact with its database. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code through the &quot;sqls&quot; argument in the /index.php/admins/Sys/addcache.html file, allowing them to potentially gain unauthorized access to the database. This can cause significant damage, such as data theft, deletion, or modification, ultimately allowing the attacker to compromise the entire system and its sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6887</cve_id>
    <title>BorG Technology Corporation｜Borg SPM 2007 - SQL Injection</title>
    <vendor>BorG Technology Corporation</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.8</score>
    <description>Borg SPM 2007 (Sales Ended in 2008) developed by BorG Technology Corporation has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-6887 vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw in the Borg SPM 2007 software, which allows hackers to inject malicious SQL code into the system. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the software, which would then execute the injected SQL commands, allowing the attacker to access and modify sensitive data. This can cause significant damage, including theft of sensitive information, data deletion, and even unauthorized changes to system settings, leading to security breaches and potential reputational harm.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6833</cve_id>
    <title>aEnrich｜a+HRD - SQL Injection</title>
    <vendor>aEnrich</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.5</score>
    <description>The a+HRD developed by aEnrich has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simplified explanation of the CVE-2026-6833 vulnerability:

The CVE-2026-6833 vulnerability is a SQL Injection flaw that lets attackers inject malicious SQL code into a database system. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request to the target system, allowing them to view sensitive database information that they shouldn't have access to. This exploit can cause significant damage by exposing sensitive data, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to the system, or even stealing confidential information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6674</cve_id>
    <title>Plugin: CMS für Motorrad Werkstätten &lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via 'arttype' Parameter</title>
    <vendor>tholstkabelbwde</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.5</score>
    <description>The Plugin: CMS für Motorrad Werkstätten plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'arttype' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6674, is an SQL Injection flaw in the CMS für Motorrad Werkstätten WordPress plugin, which allows attackers to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker with subscriber-level access or higher can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the 'arttype' parameter, which enables them to execute additional SQL queries to extract sensitive information from the database. This can lead to the theft of sensitive data, such as user credentials or financial information, giving attackers a clear path to further malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6644</cve_id>
    <title>A command injection vulnerability was found in the PPTP VPN Clients on the ADM</title>
    <vendor>ASUSTOR Inc.</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>CRITICAL</severity>
    <score>9.4</score>
    <description>A command injection vulnerability was found in the PPTP VPN Clients on the ADM. The vulnerability allows an administrative user to break out of the restricted web environment and execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system. This occurs due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input before it is passed to a system shell. Successful exploitation allows an attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) and fully compromise the system. Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.RR42 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.2.REO1.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-6644 vulnerability in simple terms:

This CVE-2026-6644 vulnerability is a type of SQL injection that allows an attacker to break into the system's command line. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the system, which is then executed without proper validation, allowing the attacker to run arbitrary code on the system. This vulnerability can cause complete system compromise, allowing the attacker to take control of the entire system, steal sensitive data, and disrupt critical services.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6629</cve_id>
    <title>Metasoft 美特软件 MetaCRM Interface sql.jsp Statement.executeUpdate sql injection</title>
    <vendor>Metasoft 美特软件</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in Metasoft 美特软件 MetaCRM up to 6.4.0. This vulnerability affects the function Statement.executeUpdate of the file sql.jsp of the component Interface. Such manipulation of the argument sql leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6629 is a SQL injection issue that affects the MetaCRM interface, specifically the &quot;sql.jsp&quot; file, in versions up to 6.4.0.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the input data in a way that allows them to inject malicious SQL code, which can be done remotely, and can bypass the security checks normally in place to prevent this kind of attack.

The damage caused by this vulnerability can include unauthorized access to or manipulation of sensitive data, potentially leading to data breaches, identity theft, or other malicious activities that could compromise the security and integrity of the affected system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6628</cve_id>
    <title>phili67 Ecclesia CRM Query Viewer view ValidateInput sql injection</title>
    <vendor>phili67</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in phili67 Ecclesia CRM up to 8.0.0. This affects the function ValidateInput of the file /v2/query/view/ of the component Query Viewer Component. This manipulation of the argument custom causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection issue in the Ecclesia CRM's Query Viewer Component that allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by inputting a specific malicious argument, &quot;custom&quot;, which bypasses the system's usual data validation and allows them to access sensitive data. If successfully exploited, this vulnerability can cause significant damage by allowing an attacker to steal, modify, or even delete sensitive data within the Ecclesia CRM system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6595</cve_id>
    <title>ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System HTTP GET Parameter buslocation.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>ProjectsAndPrograms</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file buslocation.php of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument bus_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are 3 simple sentences explaining the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL Injection attack in the ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System, specifically in the buslocation.php file, where an attacker can manipulate the &quot;bus_id&quot; parameter to inject malicious SQL code. The attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the system, allowing them to access, modify, or delete sensitive data in the database. This can cause serious damage by allowing attackers to steal sensitive information, disrupt critical operations, and compromise the integrity of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6562</cve_id>
    <title>dameng100 muucmf index.html getListByPage sql injection</title>
    <vendor>dameng100</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in dameng100 muucmf 1.9.5.20260309. Impacted is the function getListByPage of the file /index/Search/index.html. Executing a manipulation of the argument keyword can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>CVE-2026-6562 is a SQL Injection vulnerability in the dameng100 muucmf 1.9.5.20260309 system, specifically in the /index/Search/index.html file. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;keyword&quot; argument in the getListByPage function, which allows them to inject malicious SQL code and gain unauthorized access to the system. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, potentially leading to data theft, system crashes, or even a complete takeover of the affected database or system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6490</cve_id>
    <title>QueryMine sms GET Request Parameter deletecourse.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>QueryMine</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in QueryMine sms up to 7ab5a9ea196209611134525ffc18de25c57d9593. Impacted is an unknown function of the file admin/deletecourse.php of the component GET Request Parameter Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-6490 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw that allows an attacker to manipulate sensitive database queries. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted GET request to the 'admin/deletecourse.php' page, which can inject malicious SQL code, potentially allowing the attacker to access or alter sensitive information. This SQL injection can cause the attacker to steal or modify sensitive data, disrupting the functionality of the affected system and potentially putting user credentials at risk.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6488</cve_id>
    <title>QueryMine sms GET Request Parameter editcourse.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>QueryMine</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in QueryMine sms up to 7ab5a9ea196209611134525ffc18de25c57d9593. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/editcourse.php of the component GET Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE-2026-6488 vulnerability:

This vulnerability is a Sql Injection flaw that affects the admin/editcourse.php file in the QueryMine component, allowing an attacker to inject malicious SQL code by manipulating the ID request parameter.

An attacker can exploit this flaw by crafting a malicious GET request with the tainted ID parameter, which can inject malicious SQL code and potentially extract sensitive data or modify the underlying database.

The damage this vulnerability can cause includes unauthorized access to sensitive data, database tampering, and complete system compromise, potentially leading to financial loss, data breaches, or reputational damage.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6457</cve_id>
    <title>Geo Mashup &lt;= 1.13.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via 'geo_mashup_null_fields' Parameter</title>
    <vendor>cyberhobo</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.5</score>
    <description>The Geo Mashup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'geo_mashup_null_fields' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.19 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6457, is a time-based blind SQL Injection attack on the Geo Mashup plugin for WordPress, which allows attackers to extract sensitive information from the database.

Attackers exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the 'geo_mashup_null_fields' parameter, which is then used to append additional SQL queries to the existing queries, effectively allowing the attackers to manipulate the database.

The damage this vulnerability can cause includes unauthorized access to sensitive information, such as user credentials, database contents, and other confidential data, which can be used for identity theft, data breach, and other malicious activities.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6202</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Easy Blog Site post.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Easy Blog Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file post.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument tags results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE-2026-6202 vulnerability in simple terms:

CVE-2026-6202 is a SQL injection vulnerability that affects the Easy Blog Site 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate the website's database by inserting malicious SQL code. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by modifying the &quot;tags&quot; argument in the post.php file, which can lead to unauthorized access to the website's database. This vulnerability can result in damage such as data theft, website defacement, or even the ability for an attacker to take control of the website.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6193</cve_id>
    <title>PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracking System register.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>PHPGurukul</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracking System 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6193 is a SQL injection flaw in the PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracking System, version 1.1, located in the register.php file. An attacker can exploit this by sending malicious input to the &quot;email&quot; field, allowing them to manipulate the SQL queries and gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. This can lead to damage such as stolen user data, disrupted system functionality, and even full system takeover by an attacker.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6191</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Construction Management System equipments.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Construction Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /equipments.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument Name can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6191 is a SQL injection attack that occurs when an attacker manipulates the 'Name' argument in the /equipments.php file, allowing malicious input to be executed. An attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted input to the 'Name' field, which can then be used to access or modify sensitive data in the database. If not patched, this vulnerability can cause data loss, unauthorized access to sensitive information, and potential system compromise, leaving the Construction Management System vulnerable to further attacks.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6190</cve_id>
    <title>itsourcecode Construction Management System employees.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>itsourcecode</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>MEDIUM</severity>
    <score>6.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Construction Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /employees.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the CVE vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability, known as CVE-2026-6190, is a type of SQL injection that affects a web application called Construction Management System 1.0. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the &quot;Name&quot; argument in the /employees.php file, allowing them to inject malicious SQL code that can access or modify sensitive data. This exploitation can lead to unauthorized access, data theft, and potentially even complete system compromise by the attacker.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6189</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=login. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-6189 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw that allows an attacker to manipulate the &quot;Username&quot; field in an online login form, potentially accessing sensitive database information. The attacker exploits the vulnerability by inserting malicious code into the &quot;Username&quot; field to execute unauthorized SQL commands, which can be done remotely, allowing the attacker to bypass security controls. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, theft of user credentials, and potentially even compromising the entire system's security.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6188</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_sales. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6188 is a SQL injection flaw that allows an attacker to manipulate the &quot;ID&quot; argument in a request to the /ajax.php?action=delete_sales file. An attacker can exploit this flaw by entering malicious code instead of a valid ID, which can allow them to access, modify, or delete sensitive data stored in the database. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or complete system compromise, resulting in significant financial and reputational damage to the affected organization.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6187</cve_id>
    <title>SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>SourceCodester</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=chk_prod_availability. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6187, is a SQL injection flaw in the SourceCodester Pharmacy Sales and Inventory System 1.0, which allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the &quot;/ajax.php?action=chk_prod_availability&quot; page, which can trick the system into revealing sensitive data or executing unauthorized actions.

If successfully exploited, the vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, disruption of the system, and potentially even financial loss due to compromised sales and inventory information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6183</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Simple Content Management System index.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Content Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /web/index.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6183 is a SQL injection flaw in the Simple Content Management System 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate the database.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by inputting malicious data into the &quot;ID&quot; field, which can be manipulated to run unauthorized SQL commands on the database, gaining access to sensitive information. 

This vulnerability can allow the attacker to steal sensitive user data, take control of the entire system, and potentially delete or modify critical information, causing significant damage to the website and its users.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6182</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Simple Content Management System login.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Content Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /web/admin/login.php. Such manipulation of the argument User leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simplified explanation of the vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6182, is a type of SQL injection attack that occurs when an attacker manipulates a user input in a web application, specifically the &quot;User&quot; input in the /web/admin/login.php file. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request to the affected website, allowing them to potentially access sensitive data or take control of the website. This could lead to damage such as stolen user passwords, compromised website data, or even complete website takeover, giving the attacker control over sensitive information.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6167</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Faculty Management System subject-print.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Faculty Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /subject-print.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the Faculty Management System 1.0, specifically in the file /subject-print.php. The attacker exploits this flaw by manipulating the ID argument in such a way that it injects malicious SQL code, allowing them to access unauthorized data. This can cause damage by allowing the attacker to view, modify, or even delete sensitive information from the system, potentially leading to data theft or system compromise.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6166</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System UpdateVehicleFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /util/UpdateVehicleFunction.php. The manipulation of the argument VEHICLE_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's a simple explanation of the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability is a SQL injection attack, which means that an attacker can inject malicious code into the Vehicle Showroom Management System's database by manipulating a specific field called VEHICLE_ID. The attacker exploits this by entering a special type of input into the VEHICLE_ID field, allowing them to access sensitive information or even take control of the system. If the attacker is successful, they can potentially steal or modify critical data, disrupt the system's operation, or even gain access to other areas of the system that they shouldn't have access to.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6165</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System Login_check.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /util/Login_check.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The CVE-2026-6165 vulnerability is a SQL injection flaw in the code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0, located in the /util/Login_check.php file.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the ID argument in a way that can trick the system into performing unauthorized database queries, allowing them to access sensitive data or perform other malicious actions. 

This vulnerability can lead to damage such as unauthorized access to user data, system tampering, or even a complete system takeover, giving the attacker full control over the Vehicle Showroom Management System.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6164</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Lost and Found Thing Management addcat.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Lost and Found Thing Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /addcat.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument cata results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6164 is a SQL Injection flaw in the Lost and Found Thing Management 1.0 software application. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the 'cata' argument in the /addcat.php file, allowing them to execute malicious SQL commands remotely, which can potentially grant unauthorized access to sensitive data. This can cause significant damage, including data theft or deletion, and potentially even allow an attacker to take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6163</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Lost and Found Thing Management catageory.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Lost and Found Thing Management 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /catageory.php. Such manipulation of the argument cat leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6163, is a SQL injection issue in the Lost and Found Thing Management system's /catageory.php file, allowing an attacker to manipulate the &quot;cat&quot; argument in a malicious way.

An attacker exploits this weakness by injecting malicious SQL code when entering a value for the &quot;cat&quot; argument, which then gets executed by the system. The system mistakenly believes the input is genuine, unaware of the malicious intent behind it.

Once exploited, this vulnerability can cause significant damage, potentially allowing an attacker to access sensitive data, alter or delete important information, and even gain full control over the compromised system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6161</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Simple ChatBox Endpoint insert.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /chatbox/insert.php of the component Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument msg can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability CVE-2026-6161 is an SQL injection flaw in the Simple ChatBox component, which allows an attacker to manipulate the &quot;msg&quot; argument in the /chatbox/insert.php file. An attacker can exploit this flaw by injecting malicious SQL code remotely, which can allow them to access or modify sensitive data in the system. This can cause significant damage by allowing unauthorized access to user data, disrupting the chat function, and potentially allowing the attacker to take control of the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6153</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System StaffDetailsFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /util/StaffDetailsFunction.php. Such manipulation of the argument STAFF_ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here's an explanation of the vulnerability in simple terms:

The vulnerability in the Vehicle Showroom Management System is a &quot;SQL Injection&quot; flaw, which means an attacker can manipulate the database queries to access sensitive information. An attacker exploits this flaw by inserting malicious code into the &quot;STAFF_ID&quot; field, tricking the system into executing unauthorized database queries. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, allowing an attacker to steal sensitive data, modify system settings, or even gain full control over the system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6152</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System StaffAddingFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /util/StaffAddingFunction.php. This manipulation of the argument STAFF_ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description>
    <ai_explanation>CVE-2026-6152 is a SQL injection vulnerability in the Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0, specifically in the file /util/StaffAddingFunction.php.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the STAFF_ID argument in the /util/StaffAddingFunction.php file, allowing them to access and manipulate sensitive information in the database.

This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, manipulation of staff records, and potentially even disruption of the entire Vehicle Showroom Management System, resulting in compromised data and security breaches.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6151</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System PaymentStatusFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /util/PaymentStatusFunction.php. The manipulation of the argument CUSTOMER_ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6151, is a SQL injection flaw in the Vehicle Showroom Management System that allows an attacker to inject malicious SQL code. An attacker exploits this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted input, such as a CUSTOMER_ID, to the system which then unknowingly runs the malicious code, allowing the attacker to access sensitive information. This can lead to damage such as unauthorized data access, stolen customer information, or even the ability for the attacker to take control of the entire system.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6149</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System BookVehicleFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /util/BookVehicleFunction.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument BRANCH_ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>CVE-2026-6149 is a Sql Injection vulnerability that occurs in the code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0, specifically in the /util/BookVehicleFunction.php file.
The attacker exploits this vulnerability by manipulating the BRANCH_ID argument with malicious SQL code, which can give them unauthorized access to sensitive information in the database. This vulnerability can cause significant damage, including the disclosure of sensitive user data, unauthorized account creation or modification, and even complete database takeover.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6148</cve_id>
    <title>code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System MonthTotalReportUpdateFunction.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>code-projects</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /util/MonthTotalReportUpdateFunction.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument BRANCH_ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description>
    <ai_explanation>The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6148, is a SQL Injection flaw in the code-projects Vehicle Showroom Management System 1.0, allowing an attacker to manipulate user input to execute unauthorized SQL commands.

An attacker exploits this vulnerability by remotely manipulating the BRANCH_ID argument in the /util/MonthTotalReportUpdateFunction.php file, potentially allowing them to access sensitive data or disrupt the system's functionality.

The damage caused by exploiting this vulnerability can range from stealing sensitive user information to completely taking control of the system, potentially leading to financial losses, data breaches, or even system crashes.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
  <vulnerability>
    <cve_id>CVE-2026-6142</cve_id>
    <title>tushar-2223 Hotel Management System roomdelete.php sql injection</title>
    <vendor>tushar-2223</vendor>
    <attack_type>Sql Injection</attack_type>
    <severity>HIGH</severity>
    <score>7.3</score>
    <description>A vulnerability was identified in tushar-2223 Hotel Management System up to bb1f3b3666124b888f1e4bcf51b6fba9fbb01d15. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/roomdelete.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description>
    <ai_explanation>Here are three simple sentences explaining the CVE vulnerability:

The vulnerability, CVE-2026-6142, is a SQL injection attack that occurs in the &quot;roomdelete.php&quot; file of the Hotel Management System. An attacker exploits this by manipulating the &quot;ID&quot; argument to insert malicious SQL code, allowing them to access or disrupt sensitive data in the database. The damage this exploitation can cause includes unauthorized access to sensitive data, user credentials theft, and potentially even data manipulation or deletion, ultimately compromising the security and integrity of the Hotel Management System.</ai_explanation>
  </vulnerability>
</cve_explanations>
